<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Gareth Perry | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/gareth-perry/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-21T11:27:42+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Runcorn]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/11/17/bowdon-v-runcorn/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-17T09:30:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/11/17/bowdon-v-runcorn</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Better late than never. This week's report is from Mr G. Perry</p>

<p>Bowdon visited one of the most beautiful hockey grounds in West Warrington for their game against Runcorn. Dale Jago was very fortunate as it's was a home game in reality. The newly self appointed fascist dictator, Herr Mr I'm Not Sure Where I'm From Hatch gave one of the most unrousing team talks ever, pretty much destroying any morale which we had. As a direct result of such an uninspiring team talk we went one nil down. Thankfully Perry was on hand to level with a Gareth Bale-esque 59 yard weaving run and finish. Runcorn retook the lead, despite Freds dodgy touch the goal was still blamed on the captains poor prematch chat. At 2:1 Bowdon at half time the new skipper laid into his troops and got the reaction which his words commanded. A stunning second half display insued with 3 fine goals unanswered by the home team. The 4:2 final score may have flattered to deceive but in reality the discerning hockey brain knew that Bowdon had simply worn down the opposition to submission. The conclusion to the game was kindly summed up by words from Alan Hansen, a good team wins even when it is playing badly. Long may this fine run of bad form continue!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Macclesfield]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/09/23/bowdon-v-macclesfield/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-23T13:45:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/09/23/bowdon-v-macclesfield</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As promised, I have limited the report to only 3 words for each player. In short, the 6th team launched their 2013-14 league campaign in the fashion which their supporters have become accustomed to, beating Macclesfield 11-0, top go to the top of the league.</p>

<p>The following performers all played their part:</p>

<ul>
<li>Harry the Cat - watched as spectator</li>
<li>Nick West - kept Harry awake</li>
<li>Francis J. Fallon (c) - lead by example</li>
<li>Chris Gawne - got nosebleed attacking</li>
<li>Ben Fallon - over-shadowed by brother</li>
<li>Karl Bailey - Hull defeated Newcastle</li>
<li>Neil Breton - chief of assists</li>
<li>Dale Jago - mis-hit short corner</li>
<li>Andrew Braithwaite - conceded needless PC</li>
<li>Kyle Hatch - got cramp mincing</li>
<li>Gareth Perry - bankrupt after goalscoring</li>
</ul>


<p>We also had a twelfth member but I can't remember who (apologies no offence meant)? <em>- AB: it was young Ben, who had an excellent game</em></p>

<p>Many thanks to Martin Ferrett and Tony Davies for umpiring.</p>

<p><em>AB: Frank has since found out that the Macc keeper broke his leg. I'm sure you'll all join me in wishing him a speedy recovery</em></p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper left'><img class='caption' src='http://s.greenqloud.com/bowdon6/2013-09-23/top-of-the-league.png' width='734' height='355' alt='Top of the league!!!' title='Top of the league!!!'><span class='caption-text'>Top of the league!!!</span></span></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Neston Match Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-neston-match-report/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-neston-match-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This weeks guest correspondent is Girth Perry:</p>

<p>The sixth team took a 14-man squad for the tough away trip to Neston, who were one of the early pace setters, lying second in the league. The captain gave a rousing team talk, focussing on making no mistakes and using our superior fitness and skill to win the game. This wise advice was ignored by all players.</p>

<p><img class="left" src="http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/doctor.jpg" width="250" height="250" title="doctor" >
After three minutes, Fallon was tired so he minced off for a well earned break, as a punishment the skipper kept him on the bench for the rest of the game. Doctor Mosedale consulted his medical textbook and suggested rest and raising the supposedly injured ego. I’m reliably informed that had Hatch been playing, his brittle hamstrings would also have succumbed in the same period. Luckily the other 13 players were made of sterner stuff.</p>

<p>In the opening minutes Bowdon quickly registered a charity and began liberally giving away free passes to the oppo. Neston obliged and took the lead from a penalty corner (1-0). Not be undone in the set piece stakes, Branch responded for Bowdon almost immediately with a PC which owed much to the inventive creation of Perry and Brookes Snr. The move clearly dumfounded many, including Brassington, who seemed to doubt that this was a well-executed move and not a incompetent shambles!</p>

<p>The team in red and black were in the driving seat and four more goals followed before the break. A good move down the right which started at the back with Breton and West, lead to Brookes Snr passing in the D for once and Perry applied the finish. Then seeing as though it’s nearly Christmas, Neston kindly scored a couple of neat own goals for Bowdon and Brookes Jnr added a fifth.</p>

<p>The big ginger one focussed on a neater second half, with less gift wrapped passes to the opposition. Fallon, who by this time had showered, changed, done his hair and was now proudly sporting a fine Christmas jumper, failed to provide any half time oranges or any insight on the game he’d been so keenly watching. Sensibly, the skipper withdrew Perry at half time after Doctor Mosedale diagnosed acute agression syndrome.</p>

<p><img class="right" src="http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/appeal.jpg" title="appeal" >
Tactically Bowdon had the measure of their opposition and continued in their pursuit of own goals. Like a vintage West Indian pace attack, Bowdon fired repeated quick balls at the Neston defence. One one occasion, Prosser appealed for a nick behind and after correctly consulting hawk eye, the goal was awarded.</p>

<p>At 6:1 the game was surely over, however Neston scored a second goal which owed much to Jago failing to mark his man in the build-up to the goal! This fired the home team up again, however they were soon reduced to ten players after Perry was the subject of an over-zealous attempt to win the ball from him. The man advantage showed as Bowdon forced a fourth own goal of the game shortly afterwards.</p>

<p>At 7:2 tiredness crept in to much of the play from both sides, although Jeffery was the busier goalkeeper for some periods of play and happened to be in the right place at the right time on a number of occasions. McNaught was the only player not to tire, this owes much to facts which emerged well after the game. The aforementioned player has been caught half naked practicing drag flicking on his landing at 3am most mornings, accompanied by a half empty bottle of white lightening and a pack of Lambert &amp; Butler. Obviously, Dr M’s opinion will be sought before next weeks game.</p>

<p>Bowdon finished the scoring late on after Brooks Snr won a penalty flick with a Torres-esque over-elaborate swallow dive, although he had clearly been fouled. Perry converted the stroke for 8:2.</p>

<p>After the match, Branch was awarded man of the match, Jeffery came second and Manterfield a close third.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
