<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Chris Gawne | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/chris-gawne/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-28T09:41:49+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Sale]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-sale/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-09T21:42:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-sale</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Wind, rain and locked gates greeted the heroic Bowdon 6th team as they attempted to cement their top of the table position. Mindful of a tight game last time around the team buckled down quickly, moving the ball fluently and playing some liquid hockey of a standard usually only seen at international level.</p>

<p>Such was the level of concentration that your correspondent is not sure of the order of the goals scored or indeed the moves that led to them so apologies for any errors in the following.</p>

<p>Numerous chances were created and a lovely move down the right side produced the opener (I think) with the right back sliding a ball through to Breton who crossed incisively and manters got on the end of it.</p>

<p>Brooks then got the second following a scramble. That might underplay it and no doubt he will correct me if that's the case... It was a deserved goal to top off a strong performance.</p>

<p>During the first half there was a refreshing willingness from the home umpire to send off their players, although such was the professionalism of the keeper kicking the ball outside the D when Bailey was otherwise clean through that the yellow was the least that could be expected. Another yellow followed for the home team which may have been for deliberate feet, a warning that should perhaps have been taken on board by other players.</p>

<p>The high quality hockey continued and was rewarded by a third goal, this time from a short corner -a shot which may have been by Brooks being swept into the net by Braithwaite.</p>

<p>It was an excellent half of hockey against a strong team, with Grant and West contributing at the back with clearances round the post.</p>

<p>Hatch's team talk was admirably brief and included wise advice to avoid tempting the umpires to start sending our players off; advice that everyone heeded apart from the captain himself.</p>

<p>The second half proved a very different kettle of hockey sticks, with Bowdon starting slowly and allowing Sale to build some momentum. There followed a tough half with Bowdon working very hard and defending from front to back. Jeffrey was solid throughout making some good saves, but had no chance when Sale scored with around 20 minutes to go.</p>

<p>The pressure then got to Hatch who finished an energetic display 10 minutes early after cynically manoeuvring one of his enormous plates of meat to block the ball. (At least I only do it in training Kyle!) The captain was given a yellow and instantaneously awarded 'dick of the day'.</p>

<p>There was time for further clearances around and on to the post but  Bowdon held firm for the 3-1 victory.</p>

<p>All in all an excellent display with a combination of quality play and hard work throughout the team keeping Bowdon at the top of the league.</p>

<p>Joint MOM Brooks and Gawne</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Knutsford]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-knutsford/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-09T21:41:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-knutsford</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It's unforgivable not to write match reports. In my defence I was only told the week after the match and the team Xmas do had happened in the intervening period which wiped out some memory cells. So, two months later, here goes:
Knutsford is a lovely ancient market town in North Cheshire whose name comes from a river crossing  reputed to have been made by King Canute (king of England (1016–1035) and later king of Denmark, Norway and parts of Sweden as well). Having travelled via the A556 and A50 Bowdon's crack hockey team made a similar crossing but our journey is perhaps less likely to be preserved for posterity other than in this match report.</p>

<p>Then we played some hockey. There were two umpires. One of them may have been a chappess. Goals were scored by Braithwaite, Prosser, Breton, Perry and Tennant. Prosser's may have been a contender for goal of the season.</p>

<p>Our guest keeper Sam Daniel put in a solid display, communicating well with his defence. We were therefore confident when a through ball was played to our D and SD took control with a loud shout of "mine!"  Everything remained calm as SD calmly and deliberately cleared the ... WHAT?! OH FUCK HE'S KICKED IT STRAIGHT TO THE OPPO!</p>

<p>Fortunately Sam's incompetence was matched by the striker's and Sam was punished with a deserved dick of the day award and a large fine at the Xmas do rather than a goal.</p>

<p>So we won 5-1. Nice performance. Can't remember anything else I'm afraid. MOM: Gawne, apparently.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Sale]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/20/bowdon-v-sale/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-20T09:47:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/20/bowdon-v-sale</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From our correspondent Mr C. Gawne.</p>

<p>Important questions played on the minds of the brave men of Bowdon as they warmed up ahead of today’s match. Had Braithwaite and Jago found the dummies they spat last week? How would our half-a-coach cope with the uncoachables? Could anyone score a goal in the absence of our two top scorers?</p>

<p>Bowdon started quickly, with the ball going across the Sale D, begging to be finished off after only 30 seconds but with no-one able to get on the end it. Bowdon then settled down to play some good controlled hockey, passing it to each other, working hard and generally behaving like a proper hockey team. The regular back 5 were solid for the most part, with Fallon F in particular putting in some well-timed tackles. Most of the play was in the Sale end and Bowdon had the best of a competitive half. Fallon B was energetic and skilful and gave us the lead picking up a loose ball a couple of yards from the line and putting it away (disclaimer: that description might be wrong, can’t remember the goal I’m afraid, he might have beaten the whole Sale team twice and reversed it into the top corner.)</p>

<p>Sale pulled one back with a flick after a somewhat harsh decision by the umpire (but then again I’ve no qualifications). Further good play from Bowdon led to prolonged pressure which was rewarded with a Brooks D special into the top corner.</p>

<p>Bowdon therefore led 2-1 at half time. Sensible suggestions from Mr Half-a-Coach at the interval left us facing the rest of the game with renewed determination. Unfortunately Sale were quickly awarded a short and executed it perfectly, slotting a shot into the corner of the goal. Oh dear.</p>

<p>There followed a scrappy half of hockey punctuated by occasional moments of skill and unfortunately more frequent bouts of grumpiness and moaning about umpires decisions. This was of course unforgiveable, and Gawne is certainly glad that he was not involved in any of that, no siree.</p>

<p>As the game degenerated, cards started to come out. Braithwaite was assaulted by an unidentified Sale player, who was invited to play no further part in the game. It all looked to be heading towards a disappointing draw when Bowdon broke up the pitch and following a bit of a scramble Kyle was presented with a glorious chance. Death or Glory? With ice in his veins he slotted it home.</p>

<p>He then blotted his copy book somewhat, wheeling away in triumph and commencing a frankly ridiculous celebration more at home in American football than on the playing fields of Bowdon - a well-deserved dick of the day award. Whatever happened to a firm handshake, Kyle? That’s what greets all my goals. <em>(How would you know? Has it ever happened? - AB)</em></p>

<p>There was a frenetic final 7 minutes with Bowdon keeping out various short corners but repeatedly giving the ball back to Sale so that they could try again. Perhaps at training we could work on time wasting tactics. But we held on and claimed a hard fought 3-2 victory. Well played everyone.</p>

<p>Brooks D put in a last minute bid for dick of the day, swiping Gawne’s tracksuit top (and car keys) from the changing room, but fortunately in a fit of conscience owned up, whilst trying to deflect the blame on to Mosedale. Don’t worry Dave I’ve been back on to the police and assured them it was an
honest mistake. Man of the match: Gawne (unaccountably)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Llandudno]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-llandudno-2/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-llandudno-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Brought to you by Man of the Match Chris Gawne…</p>

<p>Wearily the warriors girded their loins for battle. “Can it really be a week?” complained the muscles of the ‘senior’ members of the team. No. Less than 24 hours after trudging from the pitch at the end of a glorious 0-0, the best mens’ 6th team in Bowdon were back in action.</p>

<p>Typically balmy conditions greeted us at the Dev, the mercury hitting 20C but, on the bright side, there was no snow. Llandudno had left the second longest pier in Wales and ventured into civilisation to provide today’s opposition. 15 men of Bowdon were happy to prioritise hockey over religious observance as a suitable Sunday activity, much like the soon-to-be-ex pope.</p>

<p>The Rev. Braithwaite’s team talk (sermon?) was inspirational. It had such an effect on Simon Brooks that he forgot to dress himself properly, therefore creating a new record by being rolled off before the game had started. But he was back on within 5 minutes and led a quality period of play during which Bowdon went 3-0 up in the first 25 minutes playing some of the best hockey your correspondent has seen this season; admittedly a season spent watching the 6s and 7s. Excellent goals were scored by Carl Bailey, Simon Brooks and Dale Jago, not necessarily in that order.</p>

<p>The large squad left us well able to cope with the physical demands of the match and the frequent rolling subs added fresh legs but disrupted the flow of the game and the Welsh came back into it. After a cock up in midfield Llandudo scored with a speedy break: 3-1 at half time.</p>

<p>The team talk was a riot of x rated language and tactical insight and we went into the second half reinvigorated.</p>

<p>The half began with a nip and tuck period when the match could have gone either way. Fortunately Bowdon kept it tight at the back, aided by Nick West’s well timed tackles and big feet on the goal line (never a flick!). Those barracking supporting from the sidelines roared encouragement. Eventually our superior fitness (or numbers) told and Dave Brooks and Captain Fantastic were able to add the goals needed to seal the match. I’m told that Braithwaite has now scored more goals in the opposition’s net than he has in ours – a successful season for the Skip. Francis Fallon found himself well positioned to add more goals but proved himself unable to hit a cow’s arse with a banjo, much to the enjoyment of the crowd.</p>

<p>All in all a fine victory, with the first 25 mins in particular matching the peaks of hockey prowess usually only associated with teams playing on the international stage (probably). The man of the match vote went to Gawne, more because a ‘volunteer’ was needed to write the match report than for anything done on the pitch.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
