<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Jonny Grant | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/jonny-grant/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-26T21:15:59+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Wrexham Match Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-wrexham-match-report/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-wrexham-match-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week’s guest correspondent: Mr Jonny Grant…</p>

<p>As the team entered onto the “Field of Dreams”, 4th in the league, there was great anticipation of a hat trick of victories, moral was high and our Captain lead the way giving a spirited team talk before the start of the match, 3 – 4 – 3 was the playing format.</p>

<p>Dale (The late Frank) Jago eventually “rushed” on with a minute to spare but fortunately 11 players were already warmed up and raring to go, which gave him the opportunity for an early rest on the bench.</p>

<p><img class="left" src="http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/chopping-wood.jpg" width="300" height="669">
The match started with vim and vigour and Bowdon pushing forward forcing the game into the Wrexham half. The umpires were making it clear that heavy stick tackles were not going to be tolerated, and so after a couple of green cards were issued their young Captain, who looked remarkably similar to a previously player on the same side who offended, took the brunt of the catalogue of offences and was sent off after an excellent display of chopping, which the writer had not seen the like of since a visit to Sweden in 1989 (a forest).</p>

<p>Kyle, having played the last game in full, was confident again and hopes were high of a fully fit rolling substitution tactic to keep the pressure on the oppo, but then, with not even a quarter of the match gone, injury struck.</p>

<p>It was Kyle; an awkward fall resulted in a wrist injury and he was off to the bench to wake up Dale. The team were worried for his wellbeing and evening’s entertainment but fortunately he was still able to hold his stick with his remaining hand, as was to be proven later (no picture required here Captain).</p>

<p>Wrexham pushed forward and, with a well struck ball from a tight angle, sneaked one into our goal to make the score 0 – 1.</p>

<p>The halftime whistle blew and after a further “we should be wining this” and “it’s that number 11 who is the issue” (there were two number 11s on the Wrexham side) halftime team talk the second half started with the formation 2 – 5 – 3  and again Bowdon took the advantage.</p>

<p>Although certain players were clearly tiring, and with no hope of substitution, the team battled on.  Shortly after a “professional foul” (…..what can one say…..) was given against him, it was McNaught who suffered first with a torn hamstring which sent him off limping. What was to be done?</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper right'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/medical_team.jpg' width='300' height='135' alt='The team is on standby for the next time Kyle plays…' title='The team is on standby for the next time Kyle plays…'><span class='caption-text'>The team is on standby for the next time Kyle plays…</span></span>
From the bench, with D’Artagnanesk style, Kyle was “on guard”. And, with not long to go and a flurry of flashing carbon, the ball ended up in the oppositions net to end the game 1 – 1.</p>

<p>In the end a draw was fair not the right result and we should have won. There was talk after the game that Manters had been missed but it was soon hushed up in case he found out. We than all looked forward to and talked tactics about next week’s match against the top of the table, or did we just have another beer!</p>

<p>Man of the match went to Doctor Tom for a stalwart performance, however, he was too busy mending people or something to write the match report this week, but there is always the next match.</p>

<p> </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
