<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Dave Jeffery | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/dave-jeffery/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-11-24T14:02:53+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Alderley Edge 5]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/08/bowdon-v-alderley-edge-5/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-08T20:19:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/08/bowdon-v-alderley-edge-5</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From Man of the Match Dave Jeffery...</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper left'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/cartman.jpg' width='250' height='170' alt='You will respect the Captain's Authoritah' title='You will respect the Captain's Authoritah'><span class='caption-text'>You will respect the Captain's Authoritah</span></span></p>

<p>With 2 wins under their belt the team spirits were high, even though the captain has started to blank his predecessor (thinking the power may have gone to his head already).  The team managed to turn up on time, a good start for a change.</p>

<p>After a rousing team talk the game started with possession fairly evenly split between both teams, both keepers had to be on good form with clearances at both ends in the first half, even I had a run to the edge of the D to make a quick clearance (with most of the team waiting with baited breath to see if it was going to be a clearance or a DOD nomination coming up).  As it was, a clearance was made and trouble was averted.  Down at the other end of the pitch Kyle threw his toys out of the pram and started questioning the umpires decisions (hmm someone has spent to long in Scotland?!?)</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper right'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/panic.png' width='' height='' alt='Dave moves off his line' title='Dave moves off his line'><span class='caption-text'>Dave moves off his line</span></span></p>

<p>After the game settled down Bowdon got down to business and ground out a goal (an own goal I believe), at this point we looked the better squad and were challenging for more goals, but their keeper was up to the challenge and managed to pull off some excellent saves to keep them in the game.</p>

<p>At half time it looked like Dale was about to collapse, thankfully for all after the break he was ready to stand on the pitch again. During the break we discussed tactics and someone mentioned the fact the opposition only had 10 men,  promptly after mentioning this the 11th man turned up.</p>

<p>At the start of the second half we started as we’d finished the first half, with the team in control.  This continued until the last 20 minutes where we started rotating players off the pitch and lost our shape.</p>

<p>In the last 20 minutes the opposition came back into the game and we barely got out of our half of the pitch, but against the run of play a second goal came from what looked like a cheeky chip over the keeper by Mr Brooks.  We then had to fight off a determined effort from Alderly Edge with several short corners conceded and one great save we eventually conceded a goal, but managed to hold on for a well fought 2-1 Win.</p>

<p>Without a doubt the whole team put in a great effort to pull out a good win against the team who were top of the league. Somehow man of the match was awarded to David Jeffery, and DOD was a close call between Dave Brooks and Kyle Hatch, but after careful consideration at the bar after the game Kyle has to take the award after moaning at the Umpire….</p>

<p>Onwards and Upwards for the Mighty 6’s</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
