<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: 2013 | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/2013/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-26T21:15:06+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Brooklands]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/27/bowdon-v-brooklands/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-27T16:32:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/27/bowdon-v-brooklands</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On Saturday the best Men’s 6th team in Bowdon rallied for what we knew would be a tough game against a youthful Brooklands side.</p>

<p>After starting sloppy and inviting far too much pressure from the visitors, Bowdon found there rhythm and with a nice one-two down the right hand side of the pitch Breton finished off a training ground routine that would make Jimmy proud.</p>

<p>Brooklands levelled moments later though a well worked midfield effort and a lucky deflection. 1-1</p>

<p>Bowdon rallied and Prosser regained the lead for us after a powerful Braithwaite hit into the D which was neatly deflected by Brooks into the bath of Prosser at the far post for a tap in.</p>

<p>After “Words of Wisdom” from the captain (I think he had forgotten his book) we started the second half even worse than the first, inviting too much pressure and not giving the “fans” the free flowing exciting hockey they had become accustomed to this season. This resulted in us conceding another 2 goals without reply and trailing for the first time in the game.</p>

<p>Brooks then decided to have a go from the pushback, driving at the Brooklands goal beating several players (just) and checking back onto his strong side at the top of the D to get a shot away, which was deflected nicely into the well placed Gadsby to finish off and level the game up at 3-3.</p>

<p>A forgettable end to the game after that with neither side really pushing for that all important winner in fear of conceding at the other end. Game finished 3-3 which on the balance of play was probably a fair result with Brooklands dominating large amounts of the game with no final product and Bowdon showing moments of brilliance on the counter attack along with some resolute defending from the back four.</p>

<p>MOM – Brooks
DOD – I can’t remember but it’s usually Kyle!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Sale]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-sale/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-09T21:42:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-sale</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Wind, rain and locked gates greeted the heroic Bowdon 6th team as they attempted to cement their top of the table position. Mindful of a tight game last time around the team buckled down quickly, moving the ball fluently and playing some liquid hockey of a standard usually only seen at international level.</p>

<p>Such was the level of concentration that your correspondent is not sure of the order of the goals scored or indeed the moves that led to them so apologies for any errors in the following.</p>

<p>Numerous chances were created and a lovely move down the right side produced the opener (I think) with the right back sliding a ball through to Breton who crossed incisively and manters got on the end of it.</p>

<p>Brooks then got the second following a scramble. That might underplay it and no doubt he will correct me if that's the case... It was a deserved goal to top off a strong performance.</p>

<p>During the first half there was a refreshing willingness from the home umpire to send off their players, although such was the professionalism of the keeper kicking the ball outside the D when Bailey was otherwise clean through that the yellow was the least that could be expected. Another yellow followed for the home team which may have been for deliberate feet, a warning that should perhaps have been taken on board by other players.</p>

<p>The high quality hockey continued and was rewarded by a third goal, this time from a short corner -a shot which may have been by Brooks being swept into the net by Braithwaite.</p>

<p>It was an excellent half of hockey against a strong team, with Grant and West contributing at the back with clearances round the post.</p>

<p>Hatch's team talk was admirably brief and included wise advice to avoid tempting the umpires to start sending our players off; advice that everyone heeded apart from the captain himself.</p>

<p>The second half proved a very different kettle of hockey sticks, with Bowdon starting slowly and allowing Sale to build some momentum. There followed a tough half with Bowdon working very hard and defending from front to back. Jeffrey was solid throughout making some good saves, but had no chance when Sale scored with around 20 minutes to go.</p>

<p>The pressure then got to Hatch who finished an energetic display 10 minutes early after cynically manoeuvring one of his enormous plates of meat to block the ball. (At least I only do it in training Kyle!) The captain was given a yellow and instantaneously awarded 'dick of the day'.</p>

<p>There was time for further clearances around and on to the post but  Bowdon held firm for the 3-1 victory.</p>

<p>All in all an excellent display with a combination of quality play and hard work throughout the team keeping Bowdon at the top of the league.</p>

<p>Joint MOM Brooks and Gawne</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Macclesfield]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-macclesfield/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-09T21:41:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-macclesfield</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We won, it rained!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Knutsford]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-knutsford/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-09T21:41:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-knutsford</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It's unforgivable not to write match reports. In my defence I was only told the week after the match and the team Xmas do had happened in the intervening period which wiped out some memory cells. So, two months later, here goes:
Knutsford is a lovely ancient market town in North Cheshire whose name comes from a river crossing  reputed to have been made by King Canute (king of England (1016–1035) and later king of Denmark, Norway and parts of Sweden as well). Having travelled via the A556 and A50 Bowdon's crack hockey team made a similar crossing but our journey is perhaps less likely to be preserved for posterity other than in this match report.</p>

<p>Then we played some hockey. There were two umpires. One of them may have been a chappess. Goals were scored by Braithwaite, Prosser, Breton, Perry and Tennant. Prosser's may have been a contender for goal of the season.</p>

<p>Our guest keeper Sam Daniel put in a solid display, communicating well with his defence. We were therefore confident when a through ball was played to our D and SD took control with a loud shout of "mine!"  Everything remained calm as SD calmly and deliberately cleared the ... WHAT?! OH FUCK HE'S KICKED IT STRAIGHT TO THE OPPO!</p>

<p>Fortunately Sam's incompetence was matched by the striker's and Sam was punished with a deserved dick of the day award and a large fine at the Xmas do rather than a goal.</p>

<p>So we won 5-1. Nice performance. Can't remember anything else I'm afraid. MOM: Gawne, apparently.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Crewe]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/01/05/bowdon-v-crewe/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-05T12:10:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/01/05/bowdon-v-crewe</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Match report courtesy of James Tennant...</p>

<p>This fine cloudy saturday afternoon at
south downs road, bowdon mens 6th team stepped onto the pitch. With a super early meet 40minutes before the game, a thorough team like warm up (minus mr 'under the thumb' dale) and a most inspirational talk from our esteemed captain, the first half was a bit of a disaster.....</p>

<p>One nill down at half time and play against us..oops. Without mentioning names it probably was dale's fault. 12.5 players isnt exactly idea for a top of the table clash..along with bobbly passes, standing off players in defence and an inability to transfer the ball to francis (cough JT cough).</p>

<p>After the first half 'warm up' and inspiration words from kyle, things picked up. Oh no wait...backtrack a bit. Nick, great pass to centre forward on top of the D. Good job he was scared shitless by the imposing figure of Dave in goal. Kyle - great control on the almost decapitating half volley. Dale - some fresh leg in the second half would have been good pal. Poor ben turned to 0.25 of a person.</p>

<p>Back on track...closer defending from peter helped limit the enemys attacking capability down their right side and some gutsy defending in the D limited scoring opportunities.</p>

<p>With a warmed up team, movement of the ball was much smoother peaking with some great attacking play from ben producing a 2v1 at th edge of their D. The ball reached dave brooks who slotted the ball into the bottom left of the goal. Ben, dave...jimmy would be proud.</p>

<p>A controversial goal proceeded this after some good attacking play down the right side led to a goal by andy...or was it andy? For sure, andy braithwaite takes credit with a good reverse stick chip, under pressure, over the keeper.</p>

<p>All in all a decent 2-2 result against top of the league...although another 5minutes and the enemy may have been defeated.</p>

<p>Bring on the rest of the season and good luck!! Shame dale will miss out such is life....</p>

<p>Congratulation kyle for being dick of the day.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
