<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Nick West | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://www.bowdon5.com/tags/nick-west/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://www.bowdon5.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-20T15:55:31+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://www.bowdon5.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Chester 4]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bowdon5.com/blog/2014/10/15/bowdon-v-chester-4/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-15T08:54:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bowdon5.com/blog/2014/10/15/bowdon-v-chester-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After the previous weeks heroics against the student horde of North Wales could the 5th XI continue their march up the table.</p>

<p>The drama started the day before with messages filtering through Facesplat that Carl ‘strongside’ Bailey had been locked out of his flat &amp; was in need of a home shirt.  Would he be able to aquire one &amp; get to the Grammar for the early meet-time?</p>

<p>Max remembered to bring his helmet &amp; to the shock of everyone Manters turned up for an away game, we suspect he misread the fixture a being a home game at the Grammar.  Having brushed off his protestations that Chester is not in his backyard we did point out that it wasn’t Wales &amp; a passport wouldn’t be needed.  The troops set off, whilst <del>Sergeant Wilson</del> Captain Ginger &amp; <del>Captain Mainwaring</del> Manager Kyle waited for Mr Bailey &amp; his missing shirt to arrive.</p>

<p>We arrived at Chester to be informed that Carl had still not found his shirt &amp; was still hunting for it all over South Manchester.  This forced the manager to put his kit on &amp; become part of the playing squad again, thus leaving us with 11 fit players &amp; 2 half crocked players on the bench (Ben F &amp; Kyle).</p>

<p>The game started with some good interplay by the 2 teams, noted by Jake &amp; Will linking up well.  During one of Chester’s early attacks Jiggles decided to turn his ankle leaving the 5th’s with only 11 fit players.  It was at this time that I’m reliably informed that Manters scored form ½ inch,  I think it was either Will C or it could have been from one of Jake’s jinking runs who slipped the ball past the onrushing keeper but I was distracted by Jiggles hobbling past.  During a couple of early attacks by Chester were thwarted by Max in goal &amp; the tough tackling from the defence.  Later in the first half Manters doubled his &amp; Bowdon’s goal tally this time from ¼ inch.</p>

<p>The second half started with Bowdon pushing forward &amp; Manters was surprised to receive the ball a foot out &amp; so subsequently missed out on getting his hat-trick.  Bowdon’s 3rd goal came from Ben F ghosting to the back post &amp; scoring from 2 inches out.  Late in the 2nd half Kyle decided that his presence was needed on the pitch, he muttered something about showing Manters how to score from the edge of the D.</p>

<p>Chester were thwarted at the other end by Max on multiple occasions but he was finally beaten by a well worked short corner.  Final score 3-1.</p>

<h4>Man of the match</h4>

<p>Max (another great performance from a young keeper)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Timperley]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bowdon5.com/blog/2013/10/28/bowdon-v-timperley/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-28T08:05:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bowdon5.com/blog/2013/10/28/bowdon-v-timperley</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From the imagination of Mr N West...</p>

<p>The time had arrived once again for the 6th XI to step out onto the field of play.</p>

<p>How had the young pretender managed to galvanise the Ginger Maestro's squad from a mid table team into title contenders?  Some might say it's the introduction of his younger brother,  or has his minion Kyle installed alarms in the house which allow the skipper to arrive before the rest of the squad?</p>

<p>With the news that half the usual back 4 (Disco Pete &amp; Chris G), it turned out that Dale 'The Dribbler' Jago &amp; Rick 'The Stinger' Prosser had been drafted in as defensive cover.  Could The Dribbler curb his instincts &amp; maintain the discipline needed to keep our unbeaten record intact.</p>

<p>With young Ben &amp; Andy B controlling the midfield Kyle &amp; Neil were able to advance on either flank.  Although their crosses were often met by our forward duo they were ably kept out by the athleticism of the young Timperley keeper.</p>

<p>Unfortunately Timperley did manage to bypass the Ginger Maestro &amp; Ben which meant yours truly was forced to deflect the ball skilfully (or was it luck) past our goal.  It also led to me being given a green card, apparently putting your foot into the path of the ball is not the done thing!!! <em>(I think it was probably the complete lack of subtly that did for you. Your 'Who me?' look was good though - AB)</em></p>

<p>After some good interplay between Ben &amp; Dave B the ball was put into the D for Andy Gadsby to bag a goal.  Half time score 1 0.</p>

<p>The 2nd half began with some neat interplay between Dave, Neil, Ben &amp; Andy G. These attacks were either snuffed out by the Timperley defence or put wide of the post.   Kyle decided try &amp; garner another nomination for DOTD by getting ahead of some of Neil's crosses.  Unfortunately for he lost out to Neil who let out a girly scream when the Timperley keeper launched the ball in the direction of his dodgy knee. <em>(In Neil's defence, the ball must have gone within 20m of him - AB)</em></p>

<p>Timperley managed to get forward on several occasions when Dale decided that playing at right back meant he could dribble from our own 22.  This forced both Frank &amp; myself to get stuck in &amp; again I was forced to use skill to deflect the ball just out of reach of the young whipper snapper at the far post.   It also meant that Rick had to stop the opposition right wing by stepping into the path of his run.</p>

<p>Once Kyle's Ibuprofen / Paracetamol half time energy drink kicked in 30 minutesinto the 2nd half he created an opening which Andy G neatly converted to make the score 2 0.</p>

<p>Next week we're back on the hallowed turf against Knutsford.....</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Llandudno Match Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.bowdon5.com/match-reports/bowdon-v-llandudno-match-report/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-04T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.bowdon5.com/match-reports/bowdon-v-llandudno-match-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Penned by Man of the Match Mr Nick West…</p>

<p>After the previous weeks  5-0 win (6-0 according to some sources), hopes were high of a repeat win.</p>

<p>We arrived at the club awaiting our lecture on what delights awaited us at the Longest pier in Wales.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper left'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/845_117.jpg' width='300' height='225' alt='Dave “convinces” Manters to come to Wales…' title='Dave “convinces” Manters to come to Wales…'><span class='caption-text'>Dave “convinces” Manters to come to Wales…</span></span></p>

<p>We got word from the getaway driver (Mr Jeffrey) that the target (Manters) had been spotted on his way to get a paper.  The crack kidnap squad of Messrs Brassington &amp; Prosser had been dispatched &amp; bundled the prey into the back of the Jeffrey Mobile to cries of ‘I need a passport to leave Bowdon’ they set off over the border in search of the fabled pier.</p>

<p>The rest of us headed out once the lecture had concluded,  this was only given to fill in time whilst we waited for Frank ‘The Scarlet Pimpernel’ Fallon to turn up but as of time of writing he still hasn’t been spotted.</p>

<p>Having had the passports checked at Border Control we managed to get into Wales although there were suspicious looks given to the Tall Ginger driver of one vehicle (El Capitan) as well as comments made as to what the Gaffer tape was covering up on Dale’s car.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper right'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/llandudno-pier-christopher-rowlands.jpg' width='300' height='225' alt='The longest pier in Wales!' title='The longest pier in Wales!'><span class='caption-text'>The longest pier in Wales!</span></span></p>

<p>We turned up at the pitch 45 minutes before push back &amp; the Elder Statesmen of the team were reminded of the good old days when a warm-up consisted of a Glass of port before the match rather than a hike up &amp; down a pier (it was a very long).</p>

<p>Suddenly a game of hockey broke out &amp; as usual the 6th XIV started to play the ball around rather messily allowing Llandudno time to pass the ball out to their wings &amp; get a few crosses in.  Fortunately the defence were able to re-buff these.  Mid-way through the 1st Half Lord Grant was given a green card after taking the legs away of the Oppo’s danger man (Ringer).  A while later  the same player managed to get into our D &amp; reversed sticked the ball off the post into the net 0 – 1.</p>

<p>After some poor Umpiring &amp; some generosity from Bowdon (Yours Truly) Llandudno were gifted a short corner right on Half Time from which they promptly scored 0-2.</p>

<p>After a good half time team talk Bowdon pulled themselves together &amp; Dave ‘I play better when Angry’ Brooks managed to pull one back 1-2.  Bowdon pressed for much of the second half but were unable to pull off a deserved comeback.  El Capitan managed to get a Green Card for following Lord Grant’s example &amp; taking the legs from the aforementioned danger man. This may have been due to the fact that although the floodlights were on an Umpire steadfastly refused to remove his Sunglasses……..</p>

<h3>Notable Mentions </h3>

<ul>
<li>Dave Peacock for another steadfast performance in Midfield.</li>
<li>Kyle for confounding all expectation &amp; only coming off the pitch when Subbed.</li>
</ul>


<h3>Disciplinary Matters</h3>

<ul>
<li>Lord Grant – Green Card</li>
<li>El Capitan – Green Card (should these have been Yelow?) <em>[definitely should have been a yellow - AB]</em></li>
<li>Nick W for gifting the oppo the Short Corner which led to the 2nd Llandudno Goal <em>[forgot about that one!]</em>.</li>
</ul>


<p> </p>

<p> </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
