<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-11-24T14:02:53+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Knutsford 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/28/bowdon-v-knutsford-2/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-28T07:32:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/28/bowdon-v-knutsford-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A week after a result that everybody wanted to forget, the mighty Bowdon 5th team lined up against Knutsford on what was possibly the slowest pitch known to man.</p>

<p>With the young Callum Townley at left back and James Mazarelo bringing the average age of the team down significantly, the team was eager to start and get back to winning ways.</p>

<p>The team started well and were dominant for around the first 10 minutes, pressing Knutsford early on down the right hand side through Breton and then on to Will “covers the whole pitch in his sleep” Corless on a number of occasions. Equally on the left and in the centre, Jago and Braithwaite were given some decent passes from Townley and Abbott to make Knutsford work hard to gain possession.</p>

<p>During the next 5 minutes or so, Knutsford did press hard and made West and Abbott work hard defensively. There were a couple of soft goal attempts but nothing Mazarelo couldn’t handle.</p>

<p>Then came the Doctors time to shine! Having been on the pitch for a few minutes and running around like a headless chicken, the valium that Mosedale had prescribed himself must have finally kicked in and he settled down to glide unnoticed past a defender like a ninja and get on the end of a Manterfield pass to slot in from a yard away (although the defender did try pretty hard to stop it).</p>

<p>Soon after, Braithwaite found Jago at the top of the D with a cracking pass who then managed to drag a defender out to the right and pass to Nick “Deadly from 5 yards” Manterfield to slot home Bowdon’s second.</p>

<p>After the restart Manterfield again found the back of the net after waiting for the keeper to come out and then casually flicking it through.</p>

<p>I am reliably informed that Braithwaite then got a goal but I honestly can’t remember this!</p>

<p>Knutsford did get a couple of goals back and looked Dangerous in the last 10 minutes of the game. Mosedale had an open goal and managed to hit the post which would have earned him Dick of the Day had Jago not got his feet tangled up and miss an even easier open goal attempt.</p>

<p>Special mention goes to all of the defence who had to work hard throughout the game to make sure we only conceded 2. Fallon Junior was as usual terrorizing the opposition and setting up some good moves.</p>

<h4>Man of the Match</h4>

<p>Will Corless who once again seemed to be everywhere. We need to get a heat map for him for the next game as I don’t think there is a part of the pitch he doesn’t hit!</p>

<h5>Dick of the Day Award</h5>

<p>Jago for the absolute hash of a shot on goal (if you can even call it that).  It was simply terrible.</p>

<p>Next week sees us back at Chester to take on their 5th team which will be a tough game. Let’s keep up the good work and get a solid result.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Chester 4]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/15/bowdon-v-chester-4/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-15T08:54:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/15/bowdon-v-chester-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After the previous weeks heroics against the student horde of North Wales could the 5th XI continue their march up the table.</p>

<p>The drama started the day before with messages filtering through Facesplat that Carl ‘strongside’ Bailey had been locked out of his flat &amp; was in need of a home shirt.  Would he be able to aquire one &amp; get to the Grammar for the early meet-time?</p>

<p>Max remembered to bring his helmet &amp; to the shock of everyone Manters turned up for an away game, we suspect he misread the fixture a being a home game at the Grammar.  Having brushed off his protestations that Chester is not in his backyard we did point out that it wasn’t Wales &amp; a passport wouldn’t be needed.  The troops set off, whilst <del>Sergeant Wilson</del> Captain Ginger &amp; <del>Captain Mainwaring</del> Manager Kyle waited for Mr Bailey &amp; his missing shirt to arrive.</p>

<p>We arrived at Chester to be informed that Carl had still not found his shirt &amp; was still hunting for it all over South Manchester.  This forced the manager to put his kit on &amp; become part of the playing squad again, thus leaving us with 11 fit players &amp; 2 half crocked players on the bench (Ben F &amp; Kyle).</p>

<p>The game started with some good interplay by the 2 teams, noted by Jake &amp; Will linking up well.  During one of Chester’s early attacks Jiggles decided to turn his ankle leaving the 5th’s with only 11 fit players.  It was at this time that I’m reliably informed that Manters scored form ½ inch,  I think it was either Will C or it could have been from one of Jake’s jinking runs who slipped the ball past the onrushing keeper but I was distracted by Jiggles hobbling past.  During a couple of early attacks by Chester were thwarted by Max in goal &amp; the tough tackling from the defence.  Later in the first half Manters doubled his &amp; Bowdon’s goal tally this time from ¼ inch.</p>

<p>The second half started with Bowdon pushing forward &amp; Manters was surprised to receive the ball a foot out &amp; so subsequently missed out on getting his hat-trick.  Bowdon’s 3rd goal came from Ben F ghosting to the back post &amp; scoring from 2 inches out.  Late in the 2nd half Kyle decided that his presence was needed on the pitch, he muttered something about showing Manters how to score from the edge of the D.</p>

<p>Chester were thwarted at the other end by Max on multiple occasions but he was finally beaten by a well worked short corner.  Final score 3-1.</p>

<h4>Man of the match</h4>

<p>Max (another great performance from a young keeper)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Bangor 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/08/bowdon-v-bangor-2/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-08T19:10:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/08/bowdon-v-bangor-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After last week&#8217;s titanic struggle with Alderley Edge (match report Francis?),
the finest Men&#8217;s 5th team in Bowdon needed to bounce back against Bangor Uni 2s
with a win to consolidate their league position.</p>

<p>The mighty 5s arrived early and talk quickly turned to which Bangor team would
turn up. Would it be the slightly drunk team beaten two seasons ago by the then
finest Men&#8217;s 6th team in Bowdon; or would it be the team of highly trained
athletes that beat the afore mentioned 6s later in the season. Early indications
hinted that the students meant business&#8230;</p>

<p>The students started well with a solid 10 minutes of pressure, which left this
correspondant thinking it was going to be a long afternoon. This was before the
5s wunderkind James &#8216;Mazza&#8217; Mazerello showed the students who was boss. His first
save was from point blank range, and the ball went to the student stiker&#8217;s stick.
The second save was frankly amazing, and showed that there would be no easy goals
today. The student&#8217;s heads noticably dropped and the super 5s got down to business.</p>

<p>The first goal was another well worked short corner routine (4th of the season).
The injection was wide, the pass to Bailey slow and the &#8220;cross&#8221; to Breton looping.
Breton took it in his stride and proved that he is deadly from six inches.</p>

<p>The second goal was a solo effort from new signing Jackson. He beat several students
and slotted home well, with Corless waiting for the pass that never came.</p>

<p>The third goal came from another short corner. Play Maker Braithwaite went route
one forcing the student keeper to play the ball onto his post man. Corless cooly
scored the resulting flick, giving the keeper no chance.</p>

<p>The student&#8217;s got a couple, but we won&#8217;t dwell on that&#8230;</p>

<h4>Man of the Match</h4>

<p>Mazza</p>

<h5>The Dale Jago Dick of the Day Award</h5>

<p>Frank, because Kyle decided.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon 5 v South Cheshire 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/09/21/bowdon5-v-south-cheshire-2/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-21T12:54:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/09/21/bowdon5-v-south-cheshire-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>First (long) match report of the season from our fearless leader. Never let it be said that he likes the sound of his own voice&#8230;</strong></p>

<p>A brand new season, a new division, new opposition and a new name. Bowdon 6 was now Bowdon 5, new and improved. After a successful season last year resulting in promotion. The goal this season is survival. Pre match it didn&#8217;t start well. The lose of Goal Keeper Dave Jefferies and two of the solid back four in Peter McNaught and last season Man of the Season Chris Gawne certainly didn&#8217;t help, we also lost last years quasi captain Frank Fallon, the team then lost actual captain Hatch to a stroke on Monday Night.</p>

<p>Their were positives. Some deadline day transfers were secured and two new members of the team made their league debuts. Will Corless and Ben Abbott came in to sure up the defence. Their was also a spot for the returning Ben Fallon, after a long injury. The goalkeeping crisis was solved by stealing a badger, James Mazarelo, affectionately known as Maza for typing purposes. After some interjection from Broken Captain Hatch, Acting captain Braithwaite re-jigged the line up to be:</p>

<pre><code>           Maza

Fallon, West, Abbott, Corless
         Braithwaite
      Bretton   Ankers
           Jago
   Manterfield Bailey

Subs: Prosser, Gadsby
</code></pre>

<p>New Manager Hatch took his spot on the sidelines, his personal Nurse accompanying him to make sure his blood pressure didn&#8217;t rise too high.</p>

<p>Bowdon started out surprisingly fast. Showing previous unheralded pace and verve putting today&#8217;s opposition on the back foot straight away. After being perennial slow starters last season it was a welcome surprise.</p>

<p>One other theme set early on was Cheshire understanding of how crap (slow) alty boys pitch really is. They hit everything, they might do this all the time, but today it worked wonders. Striking the ball cleanly, something Bowdon struggled with early on, a few mis-placed passes seeing the blood pressure rise.</p>

<p>Bowdon turned on the style soon, good movement down the left starting with Corless and Ankers allowed Jago to show off some skills before striking the ball inside the D, the umpire reliably informs me that the shot was going nowhere near the goal when it took a deflection off an opposition player and went in. The own goal rule now abolished any shot within the D counts if defected in, so this seasons first score was &#8230;Dale Jago. Embarrassing to the 4 strikers in the team.</p>

<p>Cheshire soon reduced themselves to 10 men, one of their players landing hard and in his eyes dislocating his shoulder. The Qualified nurse on the touchline showed no compassion and neither did Bowdon, I did try to get him ice but no one form Alty boys was around. If only they&#8217;d bought subs.</p>

<p>Bowdon pushed on however and soon started getting short corners. Nick Manterfield marked his return to the team with a nice strike into the back of the net. Cheshire finally started to play some hockey at two down and Maza was introduced to Adult Hockey after wondering what all the fuss was about. The young lad making some fine saves at both his near and far posts.</p>

<p>Bowdon capitalised on the fine work at the back by continuing to push forward earning more short corners. I&#8217;m sure the third goal was scored here, but I can&#8217;t remember who, West say, slotting home.</p>

<p>At this point Coach Brooks pointed out the good work that the team had done at training on Monday and how they were completely ignoring the tactics taught. Queue another short corner and a well worked slide ball left from Braithers, before Corless slammed home. A defender (actually) on the score sheet&#8230;.</p>

<p>It should be noted that for large portions of the first half Nick Manterfield played left back&#8230;.it was amazing to watch, not great for the blood pressure though.</p>

<p>Half Time: Bowdon 5&#8217;s 4 – 0 West Cheshire 2&#8217;s</p>

<p>After a rousing team talk and a slight tactical reshuffle. Bowdon went back out in search of more goals.</p>

<p>However it was West Cheshire who hit back first, some fine work moving the ball around the D forced a short corner from which they scored.</p>

<p>Bowdon re group quickly. Moving the ball well and with the theme of the second half being displayed regularly, both teams tiring long ball through the Swiss cheese middle creating a barrage of chances. Bowdon had to score and after a bit of a action in the middle involving Bailey, Manterfield and Prosser before Gadsby bundled home.</p>

<p>Cheshire tried to push back To stem the tide by they found keeper Maza in inspired form. Making a save with the kind of flexibility never seen before, at least not on the internet. He produced several more fantastic saves from short corners and pot shots.</p>

<p>Up next was contender for goal of the season. Another 3 on 2 break resulted in at least a short corner. From their the ball broke back to prosser at near top of the D. He lofted a slow looping ball back towards goal, the defender only needed to stand still for the ball to hit his stick but inexplicably took a Manterfield style swing and missed completely, the ball nesselled in the back of the net. Not since the opening day of last season had Bowdon scored more than 5 and they were out for blood.</p>

<p>But once again over eagerness to get the name of the score sheet cost Bowdon, far too high up the pitch a simple whack up field allowed South Cheshire to get their second of the game. Keeper Maza unfortunate to concede two.</p>

<p>Bowdon were not to be outdone and earned a questionable penalty flick. Good work from Nick Manterfield saw his burst into the D and attempt to get a shot away, an axe tackle from the wrong side should have been a short corner but referee Gareth was in a generous mode and gave a flick. Manters, checking for wind direction first, converted with ease.</p>

<p>With 15 to go, the shout went out to get more goals. Despite a number of 3 on 2 Bowdon failed to take their chance, making Manager Hatch very unhappy&#8230;.blood pressure rose.</p>

<p>Manters did hit the back of the net again, but from just inside the Yellow football D and not the white Hockey D that he insists on telling everyone. I think it was just Hat-trick avoidance.</p>

<p>The only notable last action was for Neil Bretton to regale some wood chopping actions on an opposition player, earning him the first yellow card of the season. The final whistle went seconds later and Bowdon had their first victory.</p>

<p>Final Score: Bowdon 5&#8217;s 7 – 2 South Cheshire 2&#8217;s</p>

<h4>Man of the Match</h4>

<p>For some outstanding saves: James Mazarelo</p>

<h4>The Dale Jago Dick of the Day Award</h4>

<p>Neil Bretton, Yellow card no doubting. Although Hat trick avoidance from Nick Manterfield was a close second.</p>

<p>Brilliant performance from the boys today. But it should have been double the 7 we scored. Too many 3 on 2&#8217;s. The strikers look like they never met each other. You don&#8217;t need to score all the goals. Assists are fine.</p>

<p>Lesson To learn: Look up, not all the time, just some of the time, especially when your on the ball.</p>

<p>Special thank to Andy B, for taking over this week.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Brooklands]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/27/bowdon-v-brooklands/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-27T16:32:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/27/bowdon-v-brooklands</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On Saturday the best Men’s 6th team in Bowdon rallied for what we knew would be a tough game against a youthful Brooklands side.</p>

<p>After starting sloppy and inviting far too much pressure from the visitors, Bowdon found there rhythm and with a nice one-two down the right hand side of the pitch Breton finished off a training ground routine that would make Jimmy proud.</p>

<p>Brooklands levelled moments later though a well worked midfield effort and a lucky deflection. 1-1</p>

<p>Bowdon rallied and Prosser regained the lead for us after a powerful Braithwaite hit into the D which was neatly deflected by Brooks into the bath of Prosser at the far post for a tap in.</p>

<p>After “Words of Wisdom” from the captain (I think he had forgotten his book) we started the second half even worse than the first, inviting too much pressure and not giving the “fans” the free flowing exciting hockey they had become accustomed to this season. This resulted in us conceding another 2 goals without reply and trailing for the first time in the game.</p>

<p>Brooks then decided to have a go from the pushback, driving at the Brooklands goal beating several players (just) and checking back onto his strong side at the top of the D to get a shot away, which was deflected nicely into the well placed Gadsby to finish off and level the game up at 3-3.</p>

<p>A forgettable end to the game after that with neither side really pushing for that all important winner in fear of conceding at the other end. Game finished 3-3 which on the balance of play was probably a fair result with Brooklands dominating large amounts of the game with no final product and Bowdon showing moments of brilliance on the counter attack along with some resolute defending from the back four.</p>

<p>MOM – Brooks
DOD – I can’t remember but it’s usually Kyle!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Sale]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-sale/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-09T21:42:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-sale</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Wind, rain and locked gates greeted the heroic Bowdon 6th team as they attempted to cement their top of the table position. Mindful of a tight game last time around the team buckled down quickly, moving the ball fluently and playing some liquid hockey of a standard usually only seen at international level.</p>

<p>Such was the level of concentration that your correspondent is not sure of the order of the goals scored or indeed the moves that led to them so apologies for any errors in the following.</p>

<p>Numerous chances were created and a lovely move down the right side produced the opener (I think) with the right back sliding a ball through to Breton who crossed incisively and manters got on the end of it.</p>

<p>Brooks then got the second following a scramble. That might underplay it and no doubt he will correct me if that&#8217;s the case&#8230; It was a deserved goal to top off a strong performance.</p>

<p>During the first half there was a refreshing willingness from the home umpire to send off their players, although such was the professionalism of the keeper kicking the ball outside the D when Bailey was otherwise clean through that the yellow was the least that could be expected. Another yellow followed for the home team which may have been for deliberate feet, a warning that should perhaps have been taken on board by other players.</p>

<p>The high quality hockey continued and was rewarded by a third goal, this time from a short corner -a shot which may have been by Brooks being swept into the net by Braithwaite.</p>

<p>It was an excellent half of hockey against a strong team, with Grant and West contributing at the back with clearances round the post.</p>

<p>Hatch&#8217;s team talk was admirably brief and included wise advice to avoid tempting the umpires to start sending our players off; advice that everyone heeded apart from the captain himself.</p>

<p>The second half proved a very different kettle of hockey sticks, with Bowdon starting slowly and allowing Sale to build some momentum. There followed a tough half with Bowdon working very hard and defending from front to back. Jeffrey was solid throughout making some good saves, but had no chance when Sale scored with around 20 minutes to go.</p>

<p>The pressure then got to Hatch who finished an energetic display 10 minutes early after cynically manoeuvring one of his enormous plates of meat to block the ball. (At least I only do it in training Kyle!) The captain was given a yellow and instantaneously awarded &#8216;dick of the day&#8217;.</p>

<p>There was time for further clearances around and on to the post but  Bowdon held firm for the 3-1 victory.</p>

<p>All in all an excellent display with a combination of quality play and hard work throughout the team keeping Bowdon at the top of the league.</p>

<p>Joint MOM Brooks and Gawne</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Macclesfield]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-macclesfield/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-09T21:41:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-macclesfield</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We won, it rained!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Knutsford]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-knutsford/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-09T21:41:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-knutsford</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s unforgivable not to write match reports. In my defence I was only told the week after the match and the team Xmas do had happened in the intervening period which wiped out some memory cells. So, two months later, here goes:
Knutsford is a lovely ancient market town in North Cheshire whose name comes from a river crossing  reputed to have been made by King Canute (king of England (1016–1035) and later king of Denmark, Norway and parts of Sweden as well). Having travelled via the A556 and A50 Bowdon&#8217;s crack hockey team made a similar crossing but our journey is perhaps less likely to be preserved for posterity other than in this match report.</p>

<p>Then we played some hockey. There were two umpires. One of them may have been a chappess. Goals were scored by Braithwaite, Prosser, Breton, Perry and Tennant. Prosser&#8217;s may have been a contender for goal of the season.</p>

<p>Our guest keeper Sam Daniel put in a solid display, communicating well with his defence. We were therefore confident when a through ball was played to our D and SD took control with a loud shout of &#8220;mine!&#8221;  Everything remained calm as SD calmly and deliberately cleared the &#8230; WHAT?! OH FUCK HE&#8217;S KICKED IT STRAIGHT TO THE OPPO!</p>

<p>Fortunately Sam&#8217;s incompetence was matched by the striker&#8217;s and Sam was punished with a deserved dick of the day award and a large fine at the Xmas do rather than a goal.</p>

<p>So we won 5-1. Nice performance. Can&#8217;t remember anything else I&#8217;m afraid. MOM: Gawne, apparently.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Crewe]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/01/05/bowdon-v-crewe/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-05T12:10:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/01/05/bowdon-v-crewe</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Match report courtesy of James Tennant&#8230;</p>

<p>This fine cloudy saturday afternoon at
south downs road, bowdon mens 6th team stepped onto the pitch. With a super early meet 40minutes before the game, a thorough team like warm up (minus mr &#8216;under the thumb&#8217; dale) and a most inspirational talk from our esteemed captain, the first half was a bit of a disaster&#8230;..</p>

<p>One nill down at half time and play against us..oops. Without mentioning names it probably was dale&#8217;s fault. 12.5 players isnt exactly idea for a top of the table clash..along with bobbly passes, standing off players in defence and an inability to transfer the ball to francis (cough JT cough).</p>

<p>After the first half &#8216;warm up&#8217; and inspiration words from kyle, things picked up. Oh no wait&#8230;backtrack a bit. Nick, great pass to centre forward on top of the D. Good job he was scared shitless by the imposing figure of Dave in goal. Kyle - great control on the almost decapitating half volley. Dale - some fresh leg in the second half would have been good pal. Poor ben turned to 0.25 of a person.</p>

<p>Back on track&#8230;closer defending from peter helped limit the enemys attacking capability down their right side and some gutsy defending in the D limited scoring opportunities.</p>

<p>With a warmed up team, movement of the ball was much smoother peaking with some great attacking play from ben producing a 2v1 at th edge of their D. The ball reached dave brooks who slotted the ball into the bottom left of the goal. Ben, dave&#8230;jimmy would be proud.</p>

<p>A controversial goal proceeded this after some good attacking play down the right side led to a goal by andy&#8230;or was it andy? For sure, andy braithwaite takes credit with a good reverse stick chip, under pressure, over the keeper.</p>

<p>All in all a decent 2-2 result against top of the league&#8230;although another 5minutes and the enemy may have been defeated.</p>

<p>Bring on the rest of the season and good luck!! Shame dale will miss out such is life&#8230;.</p>

<p>Congratulation kyle for being dick of the day.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Wilmslow]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/12/01/bowdon-v-wilmslow/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-01T09:50:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/12/01/bowdon-v-wilmslow</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week&#8217;s match report is brought to you by the Scottish Captain.</p>

<p>The best men’s 6th team in Bowdon travelled the long difficult journey across the M56 to Wilmslow to play a 3rds team with very varied results. Bowdon knew going into the game that with a few ill timed trips on stag do&#8217;s, exams and trips away, that the team would have a new look to it in places.</p>

<p>Thankfully three brave souls joined the current side to sure up the gaps and provide some valuable experience. With results going well for the team, hopes were high.</p>

<p>The team lined up with Jeffery in GK, Grant, West, Hawkins and McNaught across the back, Gawne on the right, Hatch left, Bray bottom and Braithwaite top of the diamond. Bailey and Gatsby were up top, leaving Prosser as super sub.</p>

<p>Bowdon started well, not put off by the slick passing of Wilmslow, putting pressure on them at 16&#8217;s and side line balls. There were some early danger signs with quick breaks from Wilmslow but the defence held firm.</p>

<p>Bowdon were playing smart hockey, making the ball do the work. The ever energetic Gatsby winning (and taking) every free hit afforded him. From this good work a fine ball in from Braithwaite allowed, Hatch to ghost in. His effort just wide.</p>

<p>The first goal of the game came against the run of play. A long hopefully lifted ball seemed to be just stopping short of running long, Nick West smartly playing the ball into the players foot. Off that bounce the Wilmslow player put the ball in the goal. Players on both teams were astounded when the home umpire gave a goal.</p>

<p>Bowdon fought to come back from that injustice, but some sloppy finishing and variable ball speed passing saw chances come and go.</p>

<p>Wilmslow 1 – 0 Bowdon</p>

<p>A timely reminder from the captain, that for the last few weeks we&#8217;d gone in from behind and come back to win, along with some strong words of encouragement and reinforcement of team principles saw Bowdon come back out refreshed.</p>

<p>It was however Wilmslow that started much the better in the second half. The central midfielders starting to dictate play moving the ball across the park very well.</p>

<p>The midfield worked incredible hard to break down the Wilmslow play, frustrating them often. But when things are going against you, they go badly against you. An unlucky ricochet, saw the ball drop to a dangerous position and the forward slotted home.</p>

<p>Two minutes later it was three. Hoping to get back into the game Bowdon pushed forward and gaps appeared. An even foot race from halfway between their left back and Hatch, saw the Bowdon captain lose&#8230;.badly. Out ran it left Grant out numbered at the back when a hit an hope ball crossed the D to be slotted home.</p>

<p>Trying to keep moral high Bowdon continued to push on. Karl Bailey was in fine form dribbling through some really poor tackles. Bowdon won a few short corners but were unable to find the goal, when on target found the Wilmslow keeper in fine form.</p>

<p>Some tired legs saw out the game, which ended in the first defeat for the mighty 6&#8217;s.</p>

<p>Full Time: Wilmslow 3 – 0 Bowdon</p>

<p>Many thanks to all involved, you gave your all in difficult conditions. Special thanks to those who stepped up in our time of need. Their is a small bonus that Crewe also lost today. But it means Sale have closed the gap.</p>

<p>Man of the Match: Andrew Braithwaite – Excellent at the top of the diamond, fought back hard and won many tackles.
Dick of the Day: The only nom was for their umpire. Mainly for the most blatant foot of the season, not knowing which way to point when he gave a foul. Not knowing how far 5 meters was and not knowing what advantage is&#8230; apart from that he was OK.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Alderley Edge 6]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/11/17/bowdon-v-alderley-edge-6/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-17T09:33:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/11/17/bowdon-v-alderley-edge-6</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From our man in Altrincham, Neil Breton</p>

<p>At Captain Kyle&#8217;s request, the squad turned up for the match 45 before push back. This meant that 15 minutes before push back we&#8217;d run out of drills to do, so a lengthy team talk resulted to fill a bit of time.</p>

<p>The first half saw the results of the practice plain for all to see: probably the worst half of hockey played all season. Poor marking, passing and only using half the pitch saw Alderley dominating possession with pass options throughout the midfield and overlaps down both sides.</p>

<p>Can&#8217;t remember the first goal, only that the guy who scored had about 10 yards of space and time to pick his spot which he duly did to deservedly give Alderley the edge (apologies). This prompted us to remember how hockey should be played, and a flowing move lead to Carl calmly rounding the keeping and finishing well on the reverse side past a guy on the line. We then forgot how to play again, allowing the Alderley player to run to the top of the D like we do at training and strike the ball 2 inches into the D (like we don&#8217;t do at training).</p>

<p>A stirring half time talk that I can&#8217;t remember sparked a typical second half revival. Much better from the off, passing was crisper, movement better and we remembered to mark when Alderley had the ball.</p>

<p>Senior Brooks remembered the right half of the pitch existed and a raking, accurate, cross field ball found your truly in acres of space. A dart into the box was followed by a nerveless (flukey) finish off the inside of the far past. Some more good play followed, with OG making another popular appearance on the scoresheet following a goalmouth scramble. Some perceived inconsistent decision making by the away umpire saw your reporter green carded for dissent (sorry team). A long range shot from someone (i was too far away to see who) flicked either an outfield player or their keeper on its way into the back of the goal (see above), meaning OG struck again.</p>

<p>4-2 was a fair result for our second half performance, and if we play as we did in the second half then we&#8217;ve a good chance next week.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Runcorn]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/11/17/bowdon-v-runcorn/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-17T09:30:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/11/17/bowdon-v-runcorn</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Better late than never. This week&#8217;s report is from Mr G. Perry</p>

<p>Bowdon visited one of the most beautiful hockey grounds in West Warrington for their game against Runcorn. Dale Jago was very fortunate as it&#8217;s was a home game in reality. The newly self appointed fascist dictator, Herr Mr I&#8217;m Not Sure Where I&#8217;m From Hatch gave one of the most unrousing team talks ever, pretty much destroying any morale which we had. As a direct result of such an uninspiring team talk we went one nil down. Thankfully Perry was on hand to level with a Gareth Bale-esque 59 yard weaving run and finish. Runcorn retook the lead, despite Freds dodgy touch the goal was still blamed on the captains poor prematch chat. At 2:1 Bowdon at half time the new skipper laid into his troops and got the reaction which his words commanded. A stunning second half display insued with 3 fine goals unanswered by the home team. The 4:2 final score may have flattered to deceive but in reality the discerning hockey brain knew that Bowdon had simply worn down the opposition to submission. The conclusion to the game was kindly summed up by words from Alan Hansen, a good team wins even when it is playing badly. Long may this fine run of bad form continue!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Timperley]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/28/bowdon-v-timperley/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-28T08:05:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/28/bowdon-v-timperley</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From the imagination of Mr N West&#8230;</p>

<p>The time had arrived once again for the 6th XI to step out onto the field of play.</p>

<p>How had the young pretender managed to galvanise the Ginger Maestro&#8217;s squad from a mid table team into title contenders?  Some might say it&#8217;s the introduction of his younger brother,  or has his minion Kyle installed alarms in the house which allow the skipper to arrive before the rest of the squad?</p>

<p>With the news that half the usual back 4 (Disco Pete &amp; Chris G), it turned out that Dale &#8216;The Dribbler&#8217; Jago &amp; Rick &#8216;The Stinger&#8217; Prosser had been drafted in as defensive cover.  Could The Dribbler curb his instincts &amp; maintain the discipline needed to keep our unbeaten record intact.</p>

<p>With young Ben &amp; Andy B controlling the midfield Kyle &amp; Neil were able to advance on either flank.  Although their crosses were often met by our forward duo they were ably kept out by the athleticism of the young Timperley keeper.</p>

<p>Unfortunately Timperley did manage to bypass the Ginger Maestro &amp; Ben which meant yours truly was forced to deflect the ball skilfully (or was it luck) past our goal.  It also led to me being given a green card, apparently putting your foot into the path of the ball is not the done thing!!! <em>(I think it was probably the complete lack of subtly that did for you. Your &#8216;Who me?&#8217; look was good though - AB)</em></p>

<p>After some good interplay between Ben &amp; Dave B the ball was put into the D for Andy Gadsby to bag a goal.  Half time score 1 0.</p>

<p>The 2nd half began with some neat interplay between Dave, Neil, Ben &amp; Andy G. These attacks were either snuffed out by the Timperley defence or put wide of the post.   Kyle decided try &amp; garner another nomination for DOTD by getting ahead of some of Neil&#8217;s crosses.  Unfortunately for he lost out to Neil who let out a girly scream when the Timperley keeper launched the ball in the direction of his dodgy knee. <em>(In Neil&#8217;s defence, the ball must have gone within 20m of him - AB)</em></p>

<p>Timperley managed to get forward on several occasions when Dale decided that playing at right back meant he could dribble from our own 22.  This forced both Frank &amp; myself to get stuck in &amp; again I was forced to use skill to deflect the ball just out of reach of the young whipper snapper at the far post.   It also meant that Rick had to stop the opposition right wing by stepping into the path of his run.</p>

<p>Once Kyle&#8217;s Ibuprofen / Paracetamol half time energy drink kicked in 30 minutesinto the 2nd half he created an opening which Andy G neatly converted to make the score 2 0.</p>

<p>Next week we&#8217;re back on the hallowed turf against Knutsford&#8230;..</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Sale]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/20/bowdon-v-sale/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-20T09:47:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/20/bowdon-v-sale</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From our correspondent Mr C. Gawne.</p>

<p>Important questions played on the minds of the brave men of Bowdon as they warmed up ahead of today’s match. Had Braithwaite and Jago found the dummies they spat last week? How would our half-a-coach cope with the uncoachables? Could anyone score a goal in the absence of our two top scorers?</p>

<p>Bowdon started quickly, with the ball going across the Sale D, begging to be finished off after only 30 seconds but with no-one able to get on the end it. Bowdon then settled down to play some good controlled hockey, passing it to each other, working hard and generally behaving like a proper hockey team. The regular back 5 were solid for the most part, with Fallon F in particular putting in some well-timed tackles. Most of the play was in the Sale end and Bowdon had the best of a competitive half. Fallon B was energetic and skilful and gave us the lead picking up a loose ball a couple of yards from the line and putting it away (disclaimer: that description might be wrong, can’t remember the goal I’m afraid, he might have beaten the whole Sale team twice and reversed it into the top corner.)</p>

<p>Sale pulled one back with a flick after a somewhat harsh decision by the umpire (but then again I’ve no qualifications). Further good play from Bowdon led to prolonged pressure which was rewarded with a Brooks D special into the top corner.</p>

<p>Bowdon therefore led 2-1 at half time. Sensible suggestions from Mr Half-a-Coach at the interval left us facing the rest of the game with renewed determination. Unfortunately Sale were quickly awarded a short and executed it perfectly, slotting a shot into the corner of the goal. Oh dear.</p>

<p>There followed a scrappy half of hockey punctuated by occasional moments of skill and unfortunately more frequent bouts of grumpiness and moaning about umpires decisions. This was of course unforgiveable, and Gawne is certainly glad that he was not involved in any of that, no siree.</p>

<p>As the game degenerated, cards started to come out. Braithwaite was assaulted by an unidentified Sale player, who was invited to play no further part in the game. It all looked to be heading towards a disappointing draw when Bowdon broke up the pitch and following a bit of a scramble Kyle was presented with a glorious chance. Death or Glory? With ice in his veins he slotted it home.</p>

<p>He then blotted his copy book somewhat, wheeling away in triumph and commencing a frankly ridiculous celebration more at home in American football than on the playing fields of Bowdon - a well-deserved dick of the day award. Whatever happened to a firm handshake, Kyle? That’s what greets all my goals. <em>(How would you know? Has it ever happened? - AB)</em></p>

<p>There was a frenetic final 7 minutes with Bowdon keeping out various short corners but repeatedly giving the ball back to Sale so that they could try again. Perhaps at training we could work on time wasting tactics. But we held on and claimed a hard fought 3-2 victory. Well played everyone.</p>

<p>Brooks D put in a last minute bid for dick of the day, swiping Gawne’s tracksuit top (and car keys) from the changing room, but fortunately in a fit of conscience owned up, whilst trying to deflect the blame on to Mosedale. Don’t worry Dave I’ve been back on to the police and assured them it was an
honest mistake. Man of the match: Gawne (unaccountably)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Brooklands]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/15/bowdon-v-brooklands/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-15T09:52:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/15/bowdon-v-brooklands</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Dave was man of the match again following this game, but I was unaccountably voted Dick of the Day so I am writing this under protest.</p>

<p>In my defence I feel I was provoked into my little tantrum at Dale. I just pointed out that I didn&#8217;t find his criticism either constructive or helpful. I may have have raised my voice a little, but under the circumstances I believe it was entirely justified.</p>

<p>Right, the game.</p>

<p>First half we sucked. Nobody could pass and everybody was in a bad mood. Brooklands dominated the first 15 - 20 minutes, but the defence put in a solid performance to keep us level. We got a bit better has the half progressed and started to make a few chances.</p>

<p>After another <del>tedious</del> inspirational team talk from the skipper (well done for being on time by the way), Bowdon came out with renewed vim and verve and started to look like the title contenders we are. Both teams made changes, but neither team could finish them. Dave made some excellent saves, once again earning a justified MoM award.</p>

<p>On the plus side, our short corners looked a bit better - we actually managed to get a couple of shots off from them and we didn&#8217;t lose and kept a clean sheet.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Alderley Edge 5]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/08/bowdon-v-alderley-edge-5/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-08T20:19:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/08/bowdon-v-alderley-edge-5</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From Man of the Match Dave Jeffery&#8230;</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper left'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/cartman.jpg' width='250' height='170' alt='You will respect the Captain's Authoritah' title='You will respect the Captain's Authoritah'><span class='caption-text'>You will respect the Captain&#8217;s Authoritah</span></span></p>

<p>With 2 wins under their belt the team spirits were high, even though the captain has started to blank his predecessor (thinking the power may have gone to his head already).  The team managed to turn up on time, a good start for a change.</p>

<p>After a rousing team talk the game started with possession fairly evenly split between both teams, both keepers had to be on good form with clearances at both ends in the first half, even I had a run to the edge of the D to make a quick clearance (with most of the team waiting with baited breath to see if it was going to be a clearance or a DOD nomination coming up).  As it was, a clearance was made and trouble was averted.  Down at the other end of the pitch Kyle threw his toys out of the pram and started questioning the umpires decisions (hmm someone has spent to long in Scotland?!?)</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper right'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/panic.png' width='' height='' alt='Dave moves off his line' title='Dave moves off his line'><span class='caption-text'>Dave moves off his line</span></span></p>

<p>After the game settled down Bowdon got down to business and ground out a goal (an own goal I believe), at this point we looked the better squad and were challenging for more goals, but their keeper was up to the challenge and managed to pull off some excellent saves to keep them in the game.</p>

<p>At half time it looked like Dale was about to collapse, thankfully for all after the break he was ready to stand on the pitch again. During the break we discussed tactics and someone mentioned the fact the opposition only had 10 men,  promptly after mentioning this the 11th man turned up.</p>

<p>At the start of the second half we started as we’d finished the first half, with the team in control.  This continued until the last 20 minutes where we started rotating players off the pitch and lost our shape.</p>

<p>In the last 20 minutes the opposition came back into the game and we barely got out of our half of the pitch, but against the run of play a second goal came from what looked like a cheeky chip over the keeper by Mr Brooks.  We then had to fight off a determined effort from Alderly Edge with several short corners conceded and one great save we eventually conceded a goal, but managed to hold on for a well fought 2-1 Win.</p>

<p>Without a doubt the whole team put in a great effort to pull out a good win against the team who were top of the league. Somehow man of the match was awarded to David Jeffery, and DOD was a close call between Dave Brooks and Kyle Hatch, but after careful consideration at the bar after the game Kyle has to take the award after moaning at the Umpire….</p>

<p>Onwards and Upwards for the Mighty 6’s</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Deeside]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/09/30/bowdon-v-deeside/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-30T09:48:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/09/30/bowdon-v-deeside</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week&#8217;s match report is brought to you by Ben Fallon:</p>

<p>Bowdon 6th team&#8217;s moral was high given their top of the league position and 11-0 thrashing of Macclesfield a week earlier. Due to Hatch&#8217;s insistence on finding a keepers kit that matched his shoes, F. Fallon, B. Fallon and Hatch arrived to the game at 12.35 for the 12.30 push back. Deeside were insistent on starting the game as soon as possible and so Bowdon began their second game of the season with eleven outfield players and no goalkeeper.</p>

<p>Despite having no goalkeeper, Bowdon enjoyed some good possession and even pressed on the attack. Bowdon worked hard to keep Deeside out of the D and even put their bodies on the line with a ball cannoning off B.Fallon&#8217;s chest. About 8 minutes into the game Hatch managed to work out how to put a goalkeeper&#8217;s kit on and ambled onto the pitch.</p>

<p>The first half was fairly open with both sides pressing for a goal. Midway through the first half, disaster struck with Deeside scoring the game&#8217;s opener, 1-0. Nevertheless, the defence were quite strong and even without any warm-up Hatch was able to pull out a couple key saves. Bowdon responded well with some good passages of play but were unable capitalise on their shortcorners.</p>

<p>After an inspirational <em>(inspirational??? - AB)</em> half-time team talk from F. Fallon, Bowdon came out second-half and took the game to Deeside. With pressure mounting, Bowdon&#8217;s equaliser came through a fantastic run by Bailey ending with an exquisite top corner finish (on his open side!), 1-1.</p>

<p>With Deeside&#8217;s age beginning to show, Bowdon were able to use their youth and superior fitness to maintain the attack. Bowdon&#8217;s persistence was rewarded when Bowdon&#8217;s new signing B. Fallon deflected in Brooks&#8217; strike at a shortcorner, 1-2.</p>

<p>The defence (Gawne, F. Fallon, West and McNaught) were solid in shutting out all of Deeside&#8217;s attacks and the midfield worked well with the attack to keep up the pressure. The icing on the cake came towards the end of the game when Jago led a superb counter-attack and released Brooks to make a cool finish, 1-3.</p>

<p>Overall, a solid performance from the sensational sixths to maintain their place at top of the table.</p>

<p>Man of the match was Ben Fallon.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Macclesfield]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/09/23/bowdon-v-macclesfield/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-23T13:45:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/09/23/bowdon-v-macclesfield</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>As promised, I have limited the report to only 3 words for each player. In short, the 6th team launched their 2013-14 league campaign in the fashion which their supporters have become accustomed to, beating Macclesfield 11-0, top go to the top of the league.</p>

<p>The following performers all played their part:</p>

<ul>
<li>Harry the Cat - watched as spectator</li>
<li>Nick West - kept Harry awake</li>
<li>Francis J. Fallon (c) - lead by example</li>
<li>Chris Gawne - got nosebleed attacking</li>
<li>Ben Fallon - over-shadowed by brother</li>
<li>Karl Bailey - Hull defeated Newcastle</li>
<li>Neil Breton - chief of assists</li>
<li>Dale Jago - mis-hit short corner</li>
<li>Andrew Braithwaite - conceded needless PC</li>
<li>Kyle Hatch - got cramp mincing</li>
<li>Gareth Perry - bankrupt after goalscoring</li>
</ul>


<p>We also had a twelfth member but I can&#8217;t remember who (apologies no offence meant)? <em>- AB: it was young Ben, who had an excellent game</em></p>

<p>Many thanks to Martin Ferrett and Tony Davies for umpiring.</p>

<p><em>AB: Frank has since found out that the Macc keeper broke his leg. I&#8217;m sure you&#8217;ll all join me in wishing him a speedy recovery</em></p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper left'><img class='caption' src='http://s.greenqloud.com/bowdon6/2013-09-23/top-of-the-league.png' width='734' height='355' alt='Top of the league!!!' title='Top of the league!!!'><span class='caption-text'>Top of the league!!!</span></span></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2012 Season Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/information/2012-season-report/"/>
    <updated>2013-05-08T14:58:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/information/2013-agm-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The sixth team have had good season this year. A solid core of players who played every week made things pretty simple for the captain.</p>

<p>The team was the best represented at club training with 6 or 7 players turning out each week. Thanks to Jimmy for attempting to get us to play hockey! I think it really did help, and we looked like we knew what we were doing a couple of times over the course of the season.</p>

<p>Results-wise we did well. Played 22, won 10, drew 4 finishing a very respectable 5th. Particularly pleasing was a positive goal difference of 11.</p>

<p>There were many highlights during the season. Neston scoring 4 own goals was helpful, and a hard fought 1 - 0 victory in Bangor stood out.</p>

<p>Our player of the season was Peter McNaught and his disco pants. Peter has improved massively as a player over the last couple of seasons. He trains every week, and I don&#8217;t think he missed a game all season.</p>

<p>Top scorer was Dave Brooks. I&#8217;m not sure what this says about us as a team, but it was a good effort.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Bebington 4]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-bebington-4/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-bebington-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week’s match report is from the Lady Doctor…</p>

<p>Bebbington 4s (maybe some 5s) vs Bowdon 6s</p>

<p>Another early start meant lie-ins were replaced with a drive to the Wirral. Some people had a longer lie-in than others, namely Frank and Kyle, but we all arrived before push back. Jago started on the side line after spending too long doing his hair in the changing room rather than warming up. (Introductory Fallon and Jago-bashing, tick)</p>

<p>Bowdon had a very shaky start to the game. Our defensive line was put under immense pressure from the beginning with a barrage of Bebbington attacks. At least 4 short corners were given against us in the first 5 minutes and all were successfully defended. A bit unnerving but no goals were conceded, god knows how!</p>

<p>The Bebbington onslaught continued for the majority of the first half with some more short corners but every attack on goal was denied. A goal line save from Captain-to-be-Fallon kept us in the game, shortly followed by a ball to the chin. Review from the team’s doctor reassured that his chin was still there. Kyle went down at one point but those dodgy hamstrings were unaffected and he was quickly back on his feet.</p>

<p>The defensive hockey skills of Si Brooks, McNaught, Fallon and West alongside the incompetence of Bebbington’s attacks maintained a score of 0-0 throughout the first half. Bowdon had limited opportunities on goal as each chance was thwarted by Bebbington’s equally strong defence.</p>

<p>El Capitan made it clear he was pleased with a 0-0 result at half time.</p>

<p>The match continued and saw better play from Bowdon with more opportunities, ball possession and control. By now, Bebbington’s cheerleaders and a 13 years young ginger lad had arrived. Braithwaite, now not the only ginger on the pitch, and Peacock managed to co-ordinate more in the midfield leading to more attacks on Bebbington. Brassington, Prosser and Mosedale struggled to secure a Bowdon goal.</p>

<p>Jago exercised his vocal cords then produced the closest attempt on goal, with a shot on target on his reverse side. Bowdon was sadly denied. Certain Bebbington players became frustrated leading to stern refereeing from Adolf Brooks, who even received a salute from a Beb player. After 60 minutes the Ginger Scouse scored making it 0-1. Fatigued Bowdon legs and some terrible man marking by Mosedale allowed Bebbington to deliver the second blow. 0-2.</p>

<p>Jeffrey certainly earnt his subs this week making some terrific saves, co-ordinating the defence and keeping Bowdon in the game. Bowdon managed to keep the score 0-2 for the last 15 minutes of the game. Despite our narrow defeat, our Ginger Captain was proud of us.</p>

<p>Match conclusion: Bowdon’s unbeaten streak comes to an honourable end and Bebbington are terrible at short corners.</p>

<p>Man of the Match: Dave Peacock for an all round solid performance, being in the right place at the right time, and giving Bowdon a strong midfield.</p>

<p>Next week we face Neston at home, who I’m sure will come seeking revenge for the 8-2 away game.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
