<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Andrew Braithwaite | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/andrew-braithwaite/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-28T07:37:16+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Bangor 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/08/bowdon-v-bangor-2/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-08T19:10:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/08/bowdon-v-bangor-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After last week's titanic struggle with Alderley Edge (match report Francis?),
the finest Men's 5th team in Bowdon needed to bounce back against Bangor Uni 2s
with a win to consolidate their league position.</p>

<p>The mighty 5s arrived early and talk quickly turned to which Bangor team would
turn up. Would it be the slightly drunk team beaten two seasons ago by the then
finest Men's 6th team in Bowdon; or would it be the team of highly trained
athletes that beat the afore mentioned 6s later in the season. Early indications
hinted that the students meant business...</p>

<p>The students started well with a solid 10 minutes of pressure, which left this
correspondant thinking it was going to be a long afternoon. This was before the
5s wunderkind James 'Mazza' Mazerello showed the students who was boss. His first
save was from point blank range, and the ball went to the student stiker's stick.
The second save was frankly amazing, and showed that there would be no easy goals
today. The student's heads noticably dropped and the super 5s got down to business.</p>

<p>The first goal was another well worked short corner routine (4th of the season).
The injection was wide, the pass to Bailey slow and the "cross" to Breton looping.
Breton took it in his stride and proved that he is deadly from six inches.</p>

<p>The second goal was a solo effort from new signing Jackson. He beat several students
and slotted home well, with Corless waiting for the pass that never came.</p>

<p>The third goal came from another short corner. Play Maker Braithwaite went route
one forcing the student keeper to play the ball onto his post man. Corless cooly
scored the resulting flick, giving the keeper no chance.</p>

<p>The student's got a couple, but we won't dwell on that...</p>

<h4>Man of the Match</h4>

<p>Mazza</p>

<h5>The Dale Jago Dick of the Day Award</h5>

<p>Frank, because Kyle decided.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Macclesfield]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-macclesfield/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-09T21:41:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-macclesfield</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We won, it rained!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Brooklands]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/15/bowdon-v-brooklands/"/>
    <updated>2013-10-15T09:52:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/10/15/bowdon-v-brooklands</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Dave was man of the match again following this game, but I was unaccountably voted Dick of the Day so I am writing this under protest.</p>

<p>In my defence I feel I was provoked into my little tantrum at Dale. I just pointed out that I didn't find his criticism either constructive or helpful. I may have have raised my voice a little, but under the circumstances I believe it was entirely justified.</p>

<p>Right, the game.</p>

<p>First half we sucked. Nobody could pass and everybody was in a bad mood. Brooklands dominated the first 15 - 20 minutes, but the defence put in a solid performance to keep us level. We got a bit better has the half progressed and started to make a few chances.</p>

<p>After another <del>tedious</del> inspirational team talk from the skipper (well done for being on time by the way), Bowdon came out with renewed vim and verve and started to look like the title contenders we are. Both teams made changes, but neither team could finish them. Dave made some excellent saves, once again earning a justified MoM award.</p>

<p>On the plus side, our short corners looked a bit better - we actually managed to get a couple of shots off from them and we didn't lose and kept a clean sheet.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2012 Season Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/information/2012-season-report/"/>
    <updated>2013-05-08T14:58:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/information/2013-agm-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The sixth team have had good season this year. A solid core of players who played every week made things pretty simple for the captain.</p>

<p>The team was the best represented at club training with 6 or 7 players turning out each week. Thanks to Jimmy for attempting to get us to play hockey! I think it really did help, and we looked like we knew what we were doing a couple of times over the course of the season.</p>

<p>Results-wise we did well. Played 22, won 10, drew 4 finishing a very respectable 5th. Particularly pleasing was a positive goal difference of 11.</p>

<p>There were many highlights during the season. Neston scoring 4 own goals was helpful, and a hard fought 1 - 0 victory in Bangor stood out.</p>

<p>Our player of the season was Peter McNaught and his disco pants. Peter has improved massively as a player over the last couple of seasons. He trains every week, and I don't think he missed a game all season.</p>

<p>Top scorer was Dave Brooks. I'm not sure what this says about us as a team, but it was a good effort.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Bebington 5]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-bebington-5/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-02T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-bebington-5</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><span class='caption-wrapper right'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/late.gif' width='' height='' alt='Guess who was late' title='Guess who was late'><span class='caption-text'>Guess who was late</span></span></p>

<p>The snows finally cleared, no earthquakes and no other acts of God. Bowdon 6th Team hockey was finally back on after a two week hiatus. Strange though it was to be playing hockey again, some things remain constant, Frank ‘the Falcon’ Fallon was yet again late getting to the club. I’ve tried fines, I’ve tried telling him a different start time to everybody else, I honestly don’t know what else to do. Perhaps he’ll turn a new leaf when he takes over as skipper next year.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper left'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/02/krays2.jpg' width='' height='' alt='The Brooks Boys' title='The Brooks Boys'><span class='caption-text'>The Brooks Boys</span></span>
Following a detailed tactical discussion with Brooks Senior on Facebook, a new look Bowdon team took to the field in a distinctly chilly Bebington. Pete McNaught moved into the midfield, with the sixth team’s very own version of the Kray twins, the Brooks boys, lining up in the centre of the defense.</p>

<p>Following yet another inspirational team talk by myself, Bowdon took to the field. It quickly became apparent that our lineup though reasonable on paper was, in practice, complete twoddle. A swift reorganization later and Bowdon began to play some decent hockey.</p>

<p>Bowdon never looked like losing the game (although we tried). Man of the Match Breton, ran like a whippet (a knackered, asthmatic whippet, but a whippet none the less) up the right wing and caused the Bebington defense problems throughout the game. Nick West thought being 0 – 0 was a bit boring so decided to kick in a short corner for Bebington, but this gave us the kick up the arse needed to get us playing. Goals by Prosser and Brooks Senior gave the Bowdon’s Premier Men’s Sixth team the win.</p>

<p>Bebington kindly provided two umpires for the match, and Brooks brothers seemed keen share their hockey experience with them to help them develop their umpiring careers. I’m not sure that this advice was all that welcome, but I’m sure they were only trying to help.</p>

<p>Both Mr West and Mr Fallon have been added to the naughty boys list. For their respective own goal and tardiness.</p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
