<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Neil Breton | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/neil-breton/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-21T11:27:42+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Alderley Edge 6]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/11/17/bowdon-v-alderley-edge-6/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-17T09:33:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/11/17/bowdon-v-alderley-edge-6</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From our man in Altrincham, Neil Breton</p>

<p>At Captain Kyle's request, the squad turned up for the match 45 before push back. This meant that 15 minutes before push back we'd run out of drills to do, so a lengthy team talk resulted to fill a bit of time.</p>

<p>The first half saw the results of the practice plain for all to see: probably the worst half of hockey played all season. Poor marking, passing and only using half the pitch saw Alderley dominating possession with pass options throughout the midfield and overlaps down both sides.</p>

<p>Can't remember the first goal, only that the guy who scored had about 10 yards of space and time to pick his spot which he duly did to deservedly give Alderley the edge (apologies). This prompted us to remember how hockey should be played, and a flowing move lead to Carl calmly rounding the keeping and finishing well on the reverse side past a guy on the line. We then forgot how to play again, allowing the Alderley player to run to the top of the D like we do at training and strike the ball 2 inches into the D (like we don't do at training).</p>

<p>A stirring half time talk that I can't remember sparked a typical second half revival. Much better from the off, passing was crisper, movement better and we remembered to mark when Alderley had the ball.</p>

<p>Senior Brooks remembered the right half of the pitch existed and a raking, accurate, cross field ball found your truly in acres of space. A dart into the box was followed by a nerveless (flukey) finish off the inside of the far past. Some more good play followed, with OG making another popular appearance on the scoresheet following a goalmouth scramble. Some perceived inconsistent decision making by the away umpire saw your reporter green carded for dissent (sorry team). A long range shot from someone (i was too far away to see who) flicked either an outfield player or their keeper on its way into the back of the goal (see above), meaning OG struck again.</p>

<p>4-2 was a fair result for our second half performance, and if we play as we did in the second half then we've a good chance next week.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon 6 v Bangor 2s]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-6-v-bangor-2s/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-06T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-6-v-bangor-2s</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Brought to you this week by Neil ‘Goal Machine’ Breton:</p>

<p><img class="left" src="http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/nw__1210757779_bangor_pier.jpg">
The second longest pier in Wales.</p>

<p>The first away match of the season saw the 6th’s embarking on a long and perilous journey to Middle Earth (if last weeks match report is to be believed). Home of Wales’ second longest pier (thanks Andy), Bangor was this week’s destination.</p>

<p>The first test of the day was the pre-dawn meet time. Unexpectedly, Fallon was the last man did arrive.</p>

<p>Despite the closure of the A55 and Andy’s insistence on using Apple maps, all 11 men made it the pitch on time and promptly set about avoiding any structured warm up or drills, preferring to watch Bangor go through their paces.</p>

<p><img class="right" src="http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/clock0945.gif">
Frank – this is what 09:45 looks like. The big hand is on 9, the little hand is between 9 and 10…</p>

<p>A rousing pre-match talk from El Capitano – “if we let them run around they might tire themselves out and we could nick a point” gave the team hope. The first half passed without incident, Bowdon’s well organised defence keeping Bangor at bay, forcing them to ping the ball sideways at the half way line without really making any progress into the Bowdon 16. Highlights included Andy intimidating a Bangor midfielder so much he threw himself to the floor in terror, and a great save from Dave from a short corner.</p>

<p>An inspirational half time speech – “we’ve not got a point yet. Yes we’ll get tired, but we can hold on” set Bowdon up for the second half. An increasingly frustrated Bangor team kept trying to pick killer passes, creating more chances as Bowden tired. Having used one of their three available substitute goalkeepers and with 2 rolling substitutes, Bangor kept pushing and enjoyed a majority of pressure and territory. This counted for nothing however when the ball got shelled up the left wing (possibly from a 16, I can’t really remember) to Neil who turned his defender like he was a line of cones at training and struck a weak shot from the top of the D that hobbled over the keepers stick at the near post. The crowd went silent, Bangor went silent, and Bowdon couldn’t believe that Breton had scored his bi-annual goal at such a key moment. 5 minutes later the ball was in the back of the net again, Andy’s reverse stick effort from 3 yards disallowed as Dave Brooks was too lazy to get out the way.</p>

<p>This fired up the Bangor team, who set up camp in the Bowdon half. Long balls out were held up well by Dave who had no support. Until he got yellow carded for a cynical goal-saving tackle. One last short corner at the final whistle gave Bangor a final role of the dice, but the shot was well saved, and Bowdon held on to steal 3 points from a gutted Bangor team.</p>

<p>Special mention must go to the two umpires who did a great job and were class.</p>

<p>Over a decent sausage and chip lunch at the local student bar, Frank Fallon was voted man of the match despite turning up late. <em>– I vetoed this, he can be MOM when he pays his fine…</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
