<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: friendly | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/friendly/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-21T11:27:42+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Didsbury v Bowdon Match Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/didsbury-v-bowdon-match-report/"/>
    <updated>2012-09-23T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/didsbury-v-bowdon-match-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My second match in charge and after last weeks debacle I had a lot to prove on the captaincy front…</p>

<p>On the plus side, we had 11 players (once Balf got out of his pit), we had opposition and we had a pitch to play on. Things were definitely looking up.</p>

<p>We had a blend of experience and more experience in the team, and I started to worry when the oppo started their warm-up drills. We should probably get some of those, but we need to be careful not to over-train.</p>

<p>The game started and it became quickly apparent that Didsbury had some game. They were strong in the midfield and good going forward. We went behind early on when I kicked ball into our goal were under the cosh of from then on.  The first half was hard and we went into the break 6 down…</p>

<p>An injury to Grinham meant that we had to borrow a player from Didsbury (thanks Ray!) and a quick reorganisation saw a different Bowdon team start the second half. We played much better and managed to keep the ball, even getting a coupleof shots in (ask Prosser about his miss). The defence worked really hard and limited to Didsbury to two goals (one was a bit of a fluke), and we showed some promising signs of hockey greatness.</p>

<p>The game finished 8-0 which I thought was a bit harsh. Didsbury are a strong team and will cause anyone they play problems this season.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
