<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Richard Prosser | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/richard-prosser/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-21T11:27:42+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Northop Hall Match Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-northop-hall-match-report/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-21T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-northop-hall-match-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Courtesy of Mr Prosser:</p>

<p>Following a win and a draw in the last two games, hopes were high for the match against Northop Hall 3s. Those hopes were soon to be dashed with the team consisting of only 10 players, Bowdon were up against it from the start.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper right'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/1937-chevy-bodie-ghost-town-21.jpg' width='300' height='300' alt='The pitch fixtureslive told us to go to…' title='The pitch fixtureslive told us to go to…'><span class='caption-text'>The pitch fixtureslive told us to go to…</span></span></p>

<p>The day didn’t get off to the best of starts after we turned up at the wrong pitch <em>(in my defence, we went where fixtureslive said the game was – Braithers) </em>. A quick call to the oppo from el Capitan and we were on our way. Turning up late for the game meant no time for that warm-up or drills that Mr Braithwaite had lined up for us… One day <em>(be careful what you wish for!)</em>.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper left'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/DepartmentStore.jpeg' width='302' height='227' alt='Where’s Fallon?' title='Where’s Fallon?'><span class='caption-text'>Where’s Fallon?</span></span></p>

<p>The first half was underway with Bowdon taking early control of the game with some neat passing through the midfield leading to one or two half chances around the D. With captain Braithwaite forced into umpiring the match, he was in no mood for messing about and gave some stern warnings to players from both sides (watch that whining Kyle). 0-0 at Half Time.</p>

<p>The second half started with some strong play from Northop Hall and the pressure paid off when they scored a rather scrappy goal. After a good save from Jeffery the ball came back at him and bobbled about a bit before a Northop Hall player tapped in the loose ball. A few good saves from short corners by Jeffery kept us within arm’s reach of a deserved draw, but after some late pressure from 10 man Bowdon it wasn’t quite enough to find the equalizer, but well-tried lads.</p>

<p>Man of the match went to Peacock for running around a lot</p>

<p>A couple of records broken on the day:<br/>
Kyle managed to get to the 65 min mark before going off with cramp and there was still no sign of Fallon….2 weeks and counting.</p>

<p>Special Thanks go to Captain Andrew Braithwaite for giving up his chance of glory to umpire the match, although he needs to find that kitty.</p>

<p>n.b.<br/>
Words that Pete Brassington wanted to be used for his performance but were highly inappropriate – Mazy, Rock, Skillful, Reliable and Lynch-pin. The only word that comes to mind for his performance is Liability.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
