<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: 2012 | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/2012/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-11-24T14:02:53+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2012 Season Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/information/2012-season-report/"/>
    <updated>2013-05-08T14:58:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/information/2013-agm-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The sixth team have had good season this year. A solid core of players who played every week made things pretty simple for the captain.</p>

<p>The team was the best represented at club training with 6 or 7 players turning out each week. Thanks to Jimmy for attempting to get us to play hockey! I think it really did help, and we looked like we knew what we were doing a couple of times over the course of the season.</p>

<p>Results-wise we did well. Played 22, won 10, drew 4 finishing a very respectable 5th. Particularly pleasing was a positive goal difference of 11.</p>

<p>There were many highlights during the season. Neston scoring 4 own goals was helpful, and a hard fought 1 - 0 victory in Bangor stood out.</p>

<p>Our player of the season was Peter McNaught and his disco pants. Peter has improved massively as a player over the last couple of seasons. He trains every week, and I don't think he missed a game all season.</p>

<p>Top scorer was Dave Brooks. I'm not sure what this says about us as a team, but it was a good effort.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Bebington 4]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-bebington-4/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-bebington-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week’s match report is from the Lady Doctor…</p>

<p>Bebbington 4s (maybe some 5s) vs Bowdon 6s</p>

<p>Another early start meant lie-ins were replaced with a drive to the Wirral. Some people had a longer lie-in than others, namely Frank and Kyle, but we all arrived before push back. Jago started on the side line after spending too long doing his hair in the changing room rather than warming up. (Introductory Fallon and Jago-bashing, tick)</p>

<p>Bowdon had a very shaky start to the game. Our defensive line was put under immense pressure from the beginning with a barrage of Bebbington attacks. At least 4 short corners were given against us in the first 5 minutes and all were successfully defended. A bit unnerving but no goals were conceded, god knows how!</p>

<p>The Bebbington onslaught continued for the majority of the first half with some more short corners but every attack on goal was denied. A goal line save from Captain-to-be-Fallon kept us in the game, shortly followed by a ball to the chin. Review from the team’s doctor reassured that his chin was still there. Kyle went down at one point but those dodgy hamstrings were unaffected and he was quickly back on his feet.</p>

<p>The defensive hockey skills of Si Brooks, McNaught, Fallon and West alongside the incompetence of Bebbington’s attacks maintained a score of 0-0 throughout the first half. Bowdon had limited opportunities on goal as each chance was thwarted by Bebbington’s equally strong defence.</p>

<p>El Capitan made it clear he was pleased with a 0-0 result at half time.</p>

<p>The match continued and saw better play from Bowdon with more opportunities, ball possession and control. By now, Bebbington’s cheerleaders and a 13 years young ginger lad had arrived. Braithwaite, now not the only ginger on the pitch, and Peacock managed to co-ordinate more in the midfield leading to more attacks on Bebbington. Brassington, Prosser and Mosedale struggled to secure a Bowdon goal.</p>

<p>Jago exercised his vocal cords then produced the closest attempt on goal, with a shot on target on his reverse side. Bowdon was sadly denied. Certain Bebbington players became frustrated leading to stern refereeing from Adolf Brooks, who even received a salute from a Beb player. After 60 minutes the Ginger Scouse scored making it 0-1. Fatigued Bowdon legs and some terrible man marking by Mosedale allowed Bebbington to deliver the second blow. 0-2.</p>

<p>Jeffrey certainly earnt his subs this week making some terrific saves, co-ordinating the defence and keeping Bowdon in the game. Bowdon managed to keep the score 0-2 for the last 15 minutes of the game. Despite our narrow defeat, our Ginger Captain was proud of us.</p>

<p>Match conclusion: Bowdon’s unbeaten streak comes to an honourable end and Bebbington are terrible at short corners.</p>

<p>Man of the Match: Dave Peacock for an all round solid performance, being in the right place at the right time, and giving Bowdon a strong midfield.</p>

<p>Next week we face Neston at home, who I’m sure will come seeking revenge for the 8-2 away game.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Wrexham]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-wrexham/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-wrexham</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From the senior Brooks…</p>

<p>We started our Saturday on a solid footing with the captain arranging a meet so we arrived in Wrexham 50mins earlier. This is the excuse I am using for everyone not quite being awake when the whistle blew to start the match.</p>

<p>The game started off very badly with us conceding a very cheap goal early on. We responded the only way we know how, with a TRAINING GROUND routine down the left hand side with JAGO PASSING <em>(I think you’ll find it was your illustrious leader!!!)</em> the ball into the centre for Brassington to divert into the back of the net 1-1. Now from here you would expect us to soldier on and take command of the game, oh no, we don’t want to make it too easy so we allow them to get another easy ball through, slicing our defence up leaving Simon Brooks on the floor and them with an easy tap in.</p>

<p>Then the cries from the back started which shook everyone to the core as nick west never shouts so it must be serious! 2 further goals from Hatch and Brooks D took us to a 3-2 lead at half time.</p>

<p>The captain was not very happy with this and gave a highly motivational speech of “your shit, we are lucky to be ahead, sort it out, we can win this”</p>

<p>We started off the second half very well, some fluid possession hockey creating some good chances when a good ball through finds Prosser who prods home to make the lead commanding.</p>

<p>Wrexham heads then started to drop and the umpires were to blame for every decision that went against them. Bowdon continued to play sublime hockey that would make the 1st team proud. Another good through ball provided Brooks D with an insight at goal and a hit towards the far corner and a Wrexham foot stops it from hitting the back of the net (or did it?), cries for FLLIIIIICKKK echoed in the umpires ears as the ball spins round the foot and into the net all by itself. Good advantage from Tony Davies.</p>

<p>Few minutes later and Wrexham had completely lost it, losing a player to a yellow card for abuse, who then preceded to try to talk his way towards a red but the umpires were forgiving in what had been a friendly game.</p>

<p>Then comes the defining moment in the match, ball fired through from Brooks S, miss trapped on the reverse by Brooks D, however, this proved advantageous as the ball popped up providing the perfect opportunity to make a simple goal look awesome as it rocketed past the keeper into the back of the net. HATRICK HERO FOR BROOKS D and Bowdon were all finished at 6-2.</p>

<p>Good Game, Brilliant second half and the perfect way to cap off a 6 game unbeaten streak!</p>

<p>Man of the Match – D Brooks</p>

<p>Dick of the Day – S Brooks (2 games in a row not being ready for the start)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Llandudno]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-llandudno-2/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-llandudno-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Brought to you by Man of the Match Chris Gawne…</p>

<p>Wearily the warriors girded their loins for battle. “Can it really be a week?” complained the muscles of the ‘senior’ members of the team. No. Less than 24 hours after trudging from the pitch at the end of a glorious 0-0, the best mens’ 6th team in Bowdon were back in action.</p>

<p>Typically balmy conditions greeted us at the Dev, the mercury hitting 20C but, on the bright side, there was no snow. Llandudno had left the second longest pier in Wales and ventured into civilisation to provide today’s opposition. 15 men of Bowdon were happy to prioritise hockey over religious observance as a suitable Sunday activity, much like the soon-to-be-ex pope.</p>

<p>The Rev. Braithwaite’s team talk (sermon?) was inspirational. It had such an effect on Simon Brooks that he forgot to dress himself properly, therefore creating a new record by being rolled off before the game had started. But he was back on within 5 minutes and led a quality period of play during which Bowdon went 3-0 up in the first 25 minutes playing some of the best hockey your correspondent has seen this season; admittedly a season spent watching the 6s and 7s. Excellent goals were scored by Carl Bailey, Simon Brooks and Dale Jago, not necessarily in that order.</p>

<p>The large squad left us well able to cope with the physical demands of the match and the frequent rolling subs added fresh legs but disrupted the flow of the game and the Welsh came back into it. After a cock up in midfield Llandudo scored with a speedy break: 3-1 at half time.</p>

<p>The team talk was a riot of x rated language and tactical insight and we went into the second half reinvigorated.</p>

<p>The half began with a nip and tuck period when the match could have gone either way. Fortunately Bowdon kept it tight at the back, aided by Nick West’s well timed tackles and big feet on the goal line (never a flick!). Those barracking supporting from the sidelines roared encouragement. Eventually our superior fitness (or numbers) told and Dave Brooks and Captain Fantastic were able to add the goals needed to seal the match. I’m told that Braithwaite has now scored more goals in the opposition’s net than he has in ours – a successful season for the Skip. Francis Fallon found himself well positioned to add more goals but proved himself unable to hit a cow’s arse with a banjo, much to the enjoyment of the crowd.</p>

<p>All in all a fine victory, with the first 25 mins in particular matching the peaks of hockey prowess usually only associated with teams playing on the international stage (probably). The man of the match vote went to Gawne, more because a ‘volunteer’ was needed to write the match report than for anything done on the pitch.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Wilmslow]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-wilmslow/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-wilmslow</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1></h1>

<p>This weeks guest correspondent, Mr P McNaught.</p>

<p>The captain was obviously worried about whether the team would have difficulty finding the unusual venue of the Dev (the team being used to prime spot in the wet pitch) and so fixed a meet time of a full half hour before the match. He didn’t need to worry as the whole team arrived before any of the opposition! In fact the opposition struggled to find the way from the Club to the Dev. This meant that the trained athletes (eg the oldies – Gaune, West and McNaught) could show off their warm up routines.This was a weakened team as el capitain had been “mugged” at selection losing key players (Breton, Grant and Peacock) to the 5th team. However, we had 3 successive wins under our belt and confidence was high. The captain repeated his usual team talk “We can beat this lot”.</p>

<p>As the snow fell, the match began badly for Bowdon who were under pressure from the beginning with lots of poor passes and appearing to lack any sense urgency. However, the team started to put a few passes together and after a rare incursion into the “D” by McNaught were awarded a short corner. This was the first of a number of short corners which the team failed to convert – clearly something to be practised at the 6th team training on Monday.</p>

<p>However, the defence of West, Prosser, Fallon and Gaunce were steady throughout and Wilmslow hardly threatened the Bowdon goal. But the Bowdon attack could not convert. Manters was unusually off target and easy chances were missed. Jago and Brooks worked hard in midfield and Braithwaite played his usual pivotal <em>(pivotal – I like that!)</em> role in the middle. However, the goals did not come and the match ended a disappointing 0-0 draw.</p>

<p>Man of the Match was Fallon (Frank the Tank) for his steady defence and incisive attack.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
