<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Dave Peacock | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/dave-peacock/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-28T09:41:49+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Wilmslow Match Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-wilmslow-match-report/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-19T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-wilmslow-match-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week’s match report is brought to by Mr Peacock and the letter Q:</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper left'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/cockermouth-0706b.jpg' width='300' height='192' alt='Apropos nothing – doesn’t Cockermouth look lovely?' title='Apropos nothing – doesn’t Cockermouth look lovely?'><span class='caption-text'>Apropos nothing – doesn’t Cockermouth look lovely?</span></span></p>

<p>The day began well for Bowdon. The team arrived on time and raring to go. Brassington applied his anti-chaffing nipple cream and the team kitted up. The aim: to continue the strong start to the season that has left the team high up the league and many of the more experienced members of the team suffering vertigo.</p>

<p>Captain Braithwaite was soon deep in to his tactical briefing. Much talk of transitions, rotation, zonal-marking, and false-nines (an oxymoron for this team surely). It was decided that the team would continue to experiment with an avant-garde 3-4-3 formation, somewhat aping the tactical shift made by Barcelona last season. Braithwaite himself was once again taking on the Busquets defensive-midfielder/spare centre-back cum libero. The talk then switched to analysis of the opposition and this was as insightful as ever – “they’ve got some old guys”.</p>

<p>Post-strategic summit, it was drills time. These clearly had the intended effect as the spectators who had thronged to watch the previous game on the pitch were soon cowed and driven away. Not a surprise, after witnessing Grant warm up by cleaving practice balls in half with his new weapon.</p>

<p>With 13 players available, it was a relief to all when hypochondriac Hatch was dispatched to the bench.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper right'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/castaway_l.jpg' width='300' height='225' alt='Neil's getting lonely on the right' title='Neil's getting lonely on the right'><span class='caption-text'>Neil's getting lonely on the right</span></span></p>

<p>Soon after the game began, it was clear that we were in for a hard game and formations and all tactics went out of the window. Poor Bretton stranded out on the right of midfield was ignored by all and sundry for most of the first half.</p>

<p>Bowdon quickly found themselves 2-1 down; at least, I think we were. The only consolation a kneed effort from converted defender Prosser. Half time brought no respite for a flagging team. Brooks had been assaulted early on, cruelly cut down in his prime, and was ruled out for the rest of the match. Manterfield, having complained pre-match of problems with his vision, now substituted himself complaining of an unspecified alcohol related condition.</p>

<p>It looked as if Bowdon were out for the count.</p>

<p>However, inspiration came from an unlikely source. Centre-back West decided to take the game by the scruff of its neck. Flowing forward a la Franz Beckenbauer, (a modern OAP version of Beckenbauer as opposed to the Kaiser in his prime, but impressive nonetheless) West soon had the opposition in disarray. Unfortunately, his teammates were also a little confused by his appearance in the opposition half for the first time this season and simply stood dumbfounded rather than going assist. Nevertheless, a brave precedent had been set and Bowdon gradually began to dominate.</p>

<p>Wilmslow soon began to panic and give away short corners. Initially, Bowdon’s efforts were as useless as normal <em>[we were lulling them into a false sense of security - AB]</em>. Suddenly, receiver Braithwaite slipped a ball to his left straight to no one. The shock of the captain passing the ball, following last week’s increasingly desperate attempts to bag a goal, soon passed and a cunning plan hatched. At the very next short corner, the ball was slipped left once more and this time Jago was there to rifle/scuffle home the equalizer.</p>

<p>Bowdon continued to push for the winner, but so did Wilmslow. Late disappointment was averted thanks to the cat like agility of Jeffery, McNaught’s dogged defensive work, and our own-goal specialist Braithwaite keeping out of the way.</p>

<p>Finally, at the death, Hatch proved his worth. Finally released from the bench thanks to the travails of Brooks and Manterfield, he had already spurned one chance by juggling like a trained monkey from an Indonesian circus rather than shooting. Thanks to Prosser he was spared eternal mockery. An insightful ball flung across the D upon which Hatch seized, flipping it over the keeper and into the net. Hatch, nee Aguero, wheeled away in celebration and the umpires soon blew for full-time.</p>

<p>Man of the Match – Prosser. Just pipping Jago by one vote. The casting vote – Prosser.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
