<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Dave Brooks | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/dave-brooks/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-28T09:41:49+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Brooklands]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/27/bowdon-v-brooklands/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-27T16:32:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/27/bowdon-v-brooklands</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On Saturday the best Men’s 6th team in Bowdon rallied for what we knew would be a tough game against a youthful Brooklands side.</p>

<p>After starting sloppy and inviting far too much pressure from the visitors, Bowdon found there rhythm and with a nice one-two down the right hand side of the pitch Breton finished off a training ground routine that would make Jimmy proud.</p>

<p>Brooklands levelled moments later though a well worked midfield effort and a lucky deflection. 1-1</p>

<p>Bowdon rallied and Prosser regained the lead for us after a powerful Braithwaite hit into the D which was neatly deflected by Brooks into the bath of Prosser at the far post for a tap in.</p>

<p>After “Words of Wisdom” from the captain (I think he had forgotten his book) we started the second half even worse than the first, inviting too much pressure and not giving the “fans” the free flowing exciting hockey they had become accustomed to this season. This resulted in us conceding another 2 goals without reply and trailing for the first time in the game.</p>

<p>Brooks then decided to have a go from the pushback, driving at the Brooklands goal beating several players (just) and checking back onto his strong side at the top of the D to get a shot away, which was deflected nicely into the well placed Gadsby to finish off and level the game up at 3-3.</p>

<p>A forgettable end to the game after that with neither side really pushing for that all important winner in fear of conceding at the other end. Game finished 3-3 which on the balance of play was probably a fair result with Brooklands dominating large amounts of the game with no final product and Bowdon showing moments of brilliance on the counter attack along with some resolute defending from the back four.</p>

<p>MOM – Brooks
DOD – I can’t remember but it’s usually Kyle!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Wrexham]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-wrexham/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-wrexham</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>From the senior Brooks…</p>

<p>We started our Saturday on a solid footing with the captain arranging a meet so we arrived in Wrexham 50mins earlier. This is the excuse I am using for everyone not quite being awake when the whistle blew to start the match.</p>

<p>The game started off very badly with us conceding a very cheap goal early on. We responded the only way we know how, with a TRAINING GROUND routine down the left hand side with JAGO PASSING <em>(I think you’ll find it was your illustrious leader!!!)</em> the ball into the centre for Brassington to divert into the back of the net 1-1. Now from here you would expect us to soldier on and take command of the game, oh no, we don’t want to make it too easy so we allow them to get another easy ball through, slicing our defence up leaving Simon Brooks on the floor and them with an easy tap in.</p>

<p>Then the cries from the back started which shook everyone to the core as nick west never shouts so it must be serious! 2 further goals from Hatch and Brooks D took us to a 3-2 lead at half time.</p>

<p>The captain was not very happy with this and gave a highly motivational speech of “your shit, we are lucky to be ahead, sort it out, we can win this”</p>

<p>We started off the second half very well, some fluid possession hockey creating some good chances when a good ball through finds Prosser who prods home to make the lead commanding.</p>

<p>Wrexham heads then started to drop and the umpires were to blame for every decision that went against them. Bowdon continued to play sublime hockey that would make the 1st team proud. Another good through ball provided Brooks D with an insight at goal and a hit towards the far corner and a Wrexham foot stops it from hitting the back of the net (or did it?), cries for FLLIIIIICKKK echoed in the umpires ears as the ball spins round the foot and into the net all by itself. Good advantage from Tony Davies.</p>

<p>Few minutes later and Wrexham had completely lost it, losing a player to a yellow card for abuse, who then preceded to try to talk his way towards a red but the umpires were forgiving in what had been a friendly game.</p>

<p>Then comes the defining moment in the match, ball fired through from Brooks S, miss trapped on the reverse by Brooks D, however, this proved advantageous as the ball popped up providing the perfect opportunity to make a simple goal look awesome as it rocketed past the keeper into the back of the net. HATRICK HERO FOR BROOKS D and Bowdon were all finished at 6-2.</p>

<p>Good Game, Brilliant second half and the perfect way to cap off a 6 game unbeaten streak!</p>

<p>Man of the Match – D Brooks</p>

<p>Dick of the Day – S Brooks (2 games in a row not being ready for the start)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Oxton 6 Match Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-oxton-6-match-report/"/>
    <updated>2012-11-12T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-oxton-6-match-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1></h1>

<p>I get the feeling that Mr Brooks isn’t a 100% happy with Mr Prosser…</p>

<p>After the abysmal week in Llandudno the team rallied to the cause to offer el captain the choice of 17 for this week’s visit of Oxton. Somehow the losing team all managed to retain their places in the squad with frank “who?” fallon making himself available, only to then hurt his hand? (do you think we haven’t noticed the new girlfriend?). Not that it mattered as he was going to the 7’s anyway.</p>

<p>The day began with the captain showing he can pass while warming up with his son <em>(the sad thing is he’s better than most of us and he’s only 7 – AB)</em>, however this appears to only be a training drill. We “welcomed” the Scousers to a warm sunny day at Alti Boys with them delaying the start as the captain felt it wasn’t fair to make them play with only 8? (SCOUSERS Braithers, SCOUSERS!!!)</p>

<p>Bowdon started off sloppy allowing the opposition to play some nice hockey for the first 30 seconds until Bretton popped up on the right hand side a drilled in a cross which MANTERS converted. And so it began….</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper left'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/surprised.jpg' width='300' height='254' alt='the crowd are somewhat surprised by Kyle’s goal…' title='the crowd are somewhat surprised by Kyle’s goal…'><span class='caption-text'>the crowd are somewhat surprised by Kyle’s goal…</span></span></p>

<p>The best 6th Team in Bowdon then started to live up to why they are the best with another 2 goal in quick succession from Manters and….wait for it…. KYLE HATCH!!!!!! Some sloppy and selfish play resulted in a 10man Bowdon side making it to half time with a clean sheet and having only scored 3! (You don’t count as playing if you don’t touch the ball Dave).</p>

<p>The second half began with Bowdon realising there is no “I” in team (unfortunately this message did not convey to the captain who just wanted to score and not pass to anyone). Brooks started on the bench and thought his ears were going as the supported, yes supporters, were commentating on DALE’S SKILL???</p>

<p>This next bit may take reading 2 or 3 times so I will put it in capitals. MANTERS THEN GOT US GOING WITH ANOTHER 2 GOALS!!!! Before Oxtons defender then decided to chip his own keeper with what was to be oxtons only shot on goal in the game. Mosedale added another for the mighty 6th team and then Brooks slotted home from close range with a ball going so slowly even Dave may have saved it. Brooks nearly doubled his tally until producing the best air shot you will see all season.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper right'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/thief.png' width='300' height='254' alt='Artists impression of Prosser’s goal' title='Artists impression of Prosser’s goal'><span class='caption-text'>Artists impression of Prosser’s goal</span></span>
Then comes the most disturbing and quite frankly unacceptable bit of camaraderie I have ever seen. It was so bad it is something I would only think of happening at Lymm and Timperley! Brooks shot at goal with a thunder of a strike only for it to hit the Oxton keeper (who must have been in some relation to the giants!) but with a lucky rebound back out to him, beat the keeper at the second attempt with a sublime drag flick which was just about to cross the line at chest height and seal off a perfect day. AND THEN… RICHARD “the honorary Scouser” PROSSER stuck a stick out to steal it for himself. Maybe he did not get the code of conduct when he joined the club but this is NOT TIMPERLEY anymore!</p>

<p>However a 9-0 win makes us all happy and we travel to Wilmslow next week with hope of another emphatic victory and a bit more team spirit (Prosser and Braithers)!</p>

<p>Unfortunately I cannot find anything this week to bully dale about, however with all his “skill” he still managed not to score and the man of the match evaded him again. With Mosedale goal and 2 assists and all round tireless performance gifting him the honour!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
