<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Mark Balfour | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/mark-balfour/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-28T07:37:16+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Crewe]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-crewe/"/>
    <updated>2012-12-20T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-crewe</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This weeks match report is brought to you by the Balfinator. There doesn’t seem to be any mention of him “going to see his parents for a minute” whilst his girlfriend had a drink with the rest of the sixth team at the club…</p>

<p>Following an uplifting 8-2 win away to Neston last week, the 6th team underwent some changes before taking on the then 3rd in the table Crewe Vagrants 3s team. Perhaps the most notable losses were the last weeks Man of the Match Branch (stolen by the 5th team), and Perry due to back problems. Other absences included the continuation of Manterfield’s phobia of any match played more than a mile from Bowdon, an unfortunate case of food poisoning that struck Prosser, and the loss of Kyle to his previously undiagnosed broken finger. Hope of adequate replacement dwindled rapidly as only Balfour  was (sort of) available to fill their shoes.</p>

<p>Well past the arranged meet time of 10:45 Fallon turned up, although it must be said that he somehow managed to arrive earlier than Jago and the Brooks brothers.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper right'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/brandy.png' width='' height='' alt='Spiced brandy and bourbon with fudge was it Frank?' title='Spiced brandy and bourbon with fudge was it Frank?'><span class='caption-text'>Spiced brandy and bourbon with fudge was it Frank?</span></span>
En route to Crewe the true tale of Balfour’s ‘availability’ emerged, as he should have been playing for the 7s later instead. With Martin’s wrath echoing throughout the north of England the 6th team finally arrived at Crewe; to find Fallon almost passed out on a table due to the strength of his hangover – the only things keeping him awake were repeating the many unusual drinks he had consumed the night before in the hope someone may find this information at all interesting, and moaning profanities about Spanish people. Timmy would have been proud of the sheer diversity of language displayed!</p>

<p>The usual lack of warm up drills, as well as the combined lateness of Fallon, Jago and Brooks (x2) and the incompetence of Balfour’s communication skills, meant that half the team hadn’t had a chance to hit a ball before the match. However the team was treated to a rousing speech by El Capitan. Bold remarks of “We can have them!” and “They aren’t as good as when we played them at the start of the season!” combined with sage words of wisdom such as “keep the ball” buoyed the team and provided mental images of a close, yet hard fought contest.</p>

<p>This rapidly turned out not to be the case…</p>

<p>Within minutes, a quick moving and well structured attack penetrated the Bowdon defence, and shortly after the ball entered the net. Moments later another Crewe goal enlightened the Bowdon team to their predicament.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper left'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/timmy.png' width='' height='' alt='Dale doesn't agree it was a flick' title='Dale doesn't agree it was a flick'><span class='caption-text'>Dale doesn't agree it was a flick</span></span>
Crewe next decided that short corners were the best way to get goals, and were awarded two within 5 minutes. Due to sterling work by the Bowdon defence though, both of these were kept out. However it was 3rd time lucky for Crewe as the ball bounced off Balfour’s stick with his attempted clearance, and struck his foot on the line. A penalty flick was awarded. All that could be heard when the team gathered was a string of swear words with no observable sentence structure or discernable meaning issuing forth from the mouth of Jago (newly christened “Timmy Tourettes”). To universal cries of “SHUT UP DALE” the team watched with growing disappointment as the flick sailed past Jeffery and into the bottom corner of the goal.</p>

<p>There were some periods of lovely passing and movement from Bowdon, although ultimately a failure to score. However the majority of the match passed in a haze of frantic defence and, to quote Braithers, “dribbling up our own arses”. Four more goals were scored in the second half, all from Crewe, and none of which deserve talking about.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper right'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/12/xray.png' width='' height='' alt='Is it broken Dr Tom? Or should he just elevate it and put some ice on?' title='Is it broken Dr Tom? Or should he just elevate it and put some ice on?'><span class='caption-text'>Is it broken Dr Tom? Or should he just elevate it and put some ice on?</span></span>
Notable moments in the match were; yet another perfectly timed save on the line from McNaught, Jago/Timmy hitting the ball 3 metres to the left of the goal when it was slipped to him on a short corner, the sudden disappearance of Braithwaite’s hitting ability, and our ‘consolation’ that the bloke whose foot Dave Brooks smashed the ball into 10 minutes from the end was STILL limping when we left the changing rooms!</p>

<p>Man of the Match was awarded to Jeffery, whose presence meant it was only 7-0, not the 20-0 it felt like. Also a team award for no own goals scored, even under such pressure.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
