<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Ben Fallon | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/ben-fallon/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-26T21:15:59+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Deeside]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/09/30/bowdon-v-deeside/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-30T09:48:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/09/30/bowdon-v-deeside</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week's match report is brought to you by Ben Fallon:</p>

<p>Bowdon 6th team's moral was high given their top of the league position and 11-0 thrashing of Macclesfield a week earlier. Due to Hatch's insistence on finding a keepers kit that matched his shoes, F. Fallon, B. Fallon and Hatch arrived to the game at 12.35 for the 12.30 push back. Deeside were insistent on starting the game as soon as possible and so Bowdon began their second game of the season with eleven outfield players and no goalkeeper.</p>

<p>Despite having no goalkeeper, Bowdon enjoyed some good possession and even pressed on the attack. Bowdon worked hard to keep Deeside out of the D and even put their bodies on the line with a ball cannoning off B.Fallon's chest. About 8 minutes into the game Hatch managed to work out how to put a goalkeeper's kit on and ambled onto the pitch.</p>

<p>The first half was fairly open with both sides pressing for a goal. Midway through the first half, disaster struck with Deeside scoring the game's opener, 1-0. Nevertheless, the defence were quite strong and even without any warm-up Hatch was able to pull out a couple key saves. Bowdon responded well with some good passages of play but were unable capitalise on their shortcorners.</p>

<p>After an inspirational <em>(inspirational??? - AB)</em> half-time team talk from F. Fallon, Bowdon came out second-half and took the game to Deeside. With pressure mounting, Bowdon's equaliser came through a fantastic run by Bailey ending with an exquisite top corner finish (on his open side!), 1-1.</p>

<p>With Deeside's age beginning to show, Bowdon were able to use their youth and superior fitness to maintain the attack. Bowdon's persistence was rewarded when Bowdon's new signing B. Fallon deflected in Brooks' strike at a shortcorner, 1-2.</p>

<p>The defence (Gawne, F. Fallon, West and McNaught) were solid in shutting out all of Deeside's attacks and the midfield worked well with the attack to keep up the pressure. The icing on the cake came towards the end of the game when Jago led a superb counter-attack and released Brooks to make a cool finish, 1-3.</p>

<p>Overall, a solid performance from the sensational sixths to maintain their place at top of the table.</p>

<p>Man of the match was Ben Fallon.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
