<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Tom Mosedale | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/tom-mosedale/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-26T21:15:59+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Bebington 4]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-bebington-4/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-bebington-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week’s match report is from the Lady Doctor…</p>

<p>Bebbington 4s (maybe some 5s) vs Bowdon 6s</p>

<p>Another early start meant lie-ins were replaced with a drive to the Wirral. Some people had a longer lie-in than others, namely Frank and Kyle, but we all arrived before push back. Jago started on the side line after spending too long doing his hair in the changing room rather than warming up. (Introductory Fallon and Jago-bashing, tick)</p>

<p>Bowdon had a very shaky start to the game. Our defensive line was put under immense pressure from the beginning with a barrage of Bebbington attacks. At least 4 short corners were given against us in the first 5 minutes and all were successfully defended. A bit unnerving but no goals were conceded, god knows how!</p>

<p>The Bebbington onslaught continued for the majority of the first half with some more short corners but every attack on goal was denied. A goal line save from Captain-to-be-Fallon kept us in the game, shortly followed by a ball to the chin. Review from the team’s doctor reassured that his chin was still there. Kyle went down at one point but those dodgy hamstrings were unaffected and he was quickly back on his feet.</p>

<p>The defensive hockey skills of Si Brooks, McNaught, Fallon and West alongside the incompetence of Bebbington’s attacks maintained a score of 0-0 throughout the first half. Bowdon had limited opportunities on goal as each chance was thwarted by Bebbington’s equally strong defence.</p>

<p>El Capitan made it clear he was pleased with a 0-0 result at half time.</p>

<p>The match continued and saw better play from Bowdon with more opportunities, ball possession and control. By now, Bebbington’s cheerleaders and a 13 years young ginger lad had arrived. Braithwaite, now not the only ginger on the pitch, and Peacock managed to co-ordinate more in the midfield leading to more attacks on Bebbington. Brassington, Prosser and Mosedale struggled to secure a Bowdon goal.</p>

<p>Jago exercised his vocal cords then produced the closest attempt on goal, with a shot on target on his reverse side. Bowdon was sadly denied. Certain Bebbington players became frustrated leading to stern refereeing from Adolf Brooks, who even received a salute from a Beb player. After 60 minutes the Ginger Scouse scored making it 0-1. Fatigued Bowdon legs and some terrible man marking by Mosedale allowed Bebbington to deliver the second blow. 0-2.</p>

<p>Jeffrey certainly earnt his subs this week making some terrific saves, co-ordinating the defence and keeping Bowdon in the game. Bowdon managed to keep the score 0-2 for the last 15 minutes of the game. Despite our narrow defeat, our Ginger Captain was proud of us.</p>

<p>Match conclusion: Bowdon’s unbeaten streak comes to an honourable end and Bebbington are terrible at short corners.</p>

<p>Man of the Match: Dave Peacock for an all round solid performance, being in the right place at the right time, and giving Bowdon a strong midfield.</p>

<p>Next week we face Neston at home, who I’m sure will come seeking revenge for the 8-2 away game.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
