<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Dale Jago | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/dale-jago/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-28T09:41:49+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Knutsford 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/28/bowdon-v-knutsford-2/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-28T07:32:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/28/bowdon-v-knutsford-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A week after a result that everybody wanted to forget, the mighty Bowdon 5th team lined up against Knutsford on what was possibly the slowest pitch known to man.</p>

<p>With the young Callum Townley at left back and James Mazarelo bringing the average age of the team down significantly, the team was eager to start and get back to winning ways.</p>

<p>The team started well and were dominant for around the first 10 minutes, pressing Knutsford early on down the right hand side through Breton and then on to Will “covers the whole pitch in his sleep” Corless on a number of occasions. Equally on the left and in the centre, Jago and Braithwaite were given some decent passes from Townley and Abbott to make Knutsford work hard to gain possession.</p>

<p>During the next 5 minutes or so, Knutsford did press hard and made West and Abbott work hard defensively. There were a couple of soft goal attempts but nothing Mazarelo couldn’t handle.</p>

<p>Then came the Doctors time to shine! Having been on the pitch for a few minutes and running around like a headless chicken, the valium that Mosedale had prescribed himself must have finally kicked in and he settled down to glide unnoticed past a defender like a ninja and get on the end of a Manterfield pass to slot in from a yard away (although the defender did try pretty hard to stop it).</p>

<p>Soon after, Braithwaite found Jago at the top of the D with a cracking pass who then managed to drag a defender out to the right and pass to Nick “Deadly from 5 yards” Manterfield to slot home Bowdon’s second.</p>

<p>After the restart Manterfield again found the back of the net after waiting for the keeper to come out and then casually flicking it through.</p>

<p>I am reliably informed that Braithwaite then got a goal but I honestly can’t remember this!</p>

<p>Knutsford did get a couple of goals back and looked Dangerous in the last 10 minutes of the game. Mosedale had an open goal and managed to hit the post which would have earned him Dick of the Day had Jago not got his feet tangled up and miss an even easier open goal attempt.</p>

<p>Special mention goes to all of the defence who had to work hard throughout the game to make sure we only conceded 2. Fallon Junior was as usual terrorizing the opposition and setting up some good moves.</p>

<h4>Man of the Match</h4>

<p>Will Corless who once again seemed to be everywhere. We need to get a heat map for him for the next game as I don’t think there is a part of the pitch he doesn’t hit!</p>

<h5>Dick of the Day Award</h5>

<p>Jago for the absolute hash of a shot on goal (if you can even call it that).  It was simply terrible.</p>

<p>Next week sees us back at Chester to take on their 5th team which will be a tough game. Let’s keep up the good work and get a solid result.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Bebington 5 Match Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-bebington-5-match-report/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-28T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-bebington-5-match-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week brought to you by Mr Dale Jago:</p>

<p>After a loss last week under difficult circumstances the sixth team were looking for a convincing win to boost morale.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper left'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/condorman.jpg' width='256' height='184' alt='Still no sign of Frank ‘the Condor’ Fallon.' title='Still no sign of Frank ‘the Condor’ Fallon.'><span class='caption-text'>Still no sign of Frank ‘the Condor’ Fallon.</span></span></p>

<p>Good news from the start was that we had 13 players and no Kyle meaning we had a good chance of still having 13 standing at full time.</p>

<p>Once again no warm up drills were organised which most people were relieved at as they didn’t want Jago showing them up with his immense pace (shameless plug, had to do it).</p>

<p>The first half started with some messy play from both teams for the first 5 minutes until Bowdon got focused and started to pass the ball around nicely using the width of the pitch well.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper right'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/Ambulance-Tory-Britain-001.jpg' width='230' height='138' alt='The new sixth team bus' title='The new sixth team bus'><span class='caption-text'>The new sixth team bus</span></span></p>

<p>The hope of still having 13 players come full time was quickly destroyed with Gawne going off after pulling something or other (Kyle Mk 2?).</p>

<p>Bowdon started to show some dominance with several chances up front and at about 10 minutes in it paid off with Manterfield finding the goal (yes that’s right Manterfield!).</p>

<p>After the restart Bowdon kept the pressure on and not long afterwards were rewarded again as Peacock skilfully beat a defender and selflessly laid the ball on to Jago who struck the ball cleanly (must have been an accident) putting it in the bottom left corner to make it 2-0.</p>

<p>After a poor attempt from a previous short corner Braithwaite stepped up looking to make amends and he didn’t disappoint, hitting the ball with some serious clout to make it 3-0 just before the half time whistle went.</p>

<p>The second half started with Bowdon not looking as sharp as they did in the first with Bebington having a good few chances. Cleverly at half time the master tactician that is Andrew ‘El Capitan’ Braithwaite had moved David ‘The Rock’ Brooks to Centre Back meaning that all of these chances were fruitless as Brooks had their Centre Forward in his pocket the whole time.</p>

<p>Bowdon managed to get another 2 goals courtesy of Manterfield again and Pritchard who was making his annual appearance.</p>

<p><strong>Final Score – Bowdon 5 – 0 Bebington</strong></p>

<p>Man of the match went to David Brooks for his solid defensive performance and making good use of the 16’s.</p>

<p>A special mention goes to Ben Scholfield for giving the team some much needed pace on the wing and up front.</p>

<p>Next week’s fixture is against Llandudno away – I have a funny feeling that Manterfield will be unavailable!</p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
