<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Dale Jago | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/dale-jago/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-26T21:15:06+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Bebington 5 Match Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-bebington-5-match-report/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-28T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-bebington-5-match-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week brought to you by Mr Dale Jago:</p>

<p>After a loss last week under difficult circumstances the sixth team were looking for a convincing win to boost morale.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper left'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/condorman.jpg' width='256' height='184' alt='Still no sign of Frank ‘the Condor’ Fallon.' title='Still no sign of Frank ‘the Condor’ Fallon.'><span class='caption-text'>Still no sign of Frank ‘the Condor’ Fallon.</span></span></p>

<p>Good news from the start was that we had 13 players and no Kyle meaning we had a good chance of still having 13 standing at full time.</p>

<p>Once again no warm up drills were organised which most people were relieved at as they didn’t want Jago showing them up with his immense pace (shameless plug, had to do it).</p>

<p>The first half started with some messy play from both teams for the first 5 minutes until Bowdon got focused and started to pass the ball around nicely using the width of the pitch well.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper right'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/Ambulance-Tory-Britain-001.jpg' width='230' height='138' alt='The new sixth team bus' title='The new sixth team bus'><span class='caption-text'>The new sixth team bus</span></span></p>

<p>The hope of still having 13 players come full time was quickly destroyed with Gawne going off after pulling something or other (Kyle Mk 2?).</p>

<p>Bowdon started to show some dominance with several chances up front and at about 10 minutes in it paid off with Manterfield finding the goal (yes that’s right Manterfield!).</p>

<p>After the restart Bowdon kept the pressure on and not long afterwards were rewarded again as Peacock skilfully beat a defender and selflessly laid the ball on to Jago who struck the ball cleanly (must have been an accident) putting it in the bottom left corner to make it 2-0.</p>

<p>After a poor attempt from a previous short corner Braithwaite stepped up looking to make amends and he didn’t disappoint, hitting the ball with some serious clout to make it 3-0 just before the half time whistle went.</p>

<p>The second half started with Bowdon not looking as sharp as they did in the first with Bebington having a good few chances. Cleverly at half time the master tactician that is Andrew ‘El Capitan’ Braithwaite had moved David ‘The Rock’ Brooks to Centre Back meaning that all of these chances were fruitless as Brooks had their Centre Forward in his pocket the whole time.</p>

<p>Bowdon managed to get another 2 goals courtesy of Manterfield again and Pritchard who was making his annual appearance.</p>

<p><strong>Final Score – Bowdon 5 – 0 Bebington</strong></p>

<p>Man of the match went to David Brooks for his solid defensive performance and making good use of the 16’s.</p>

<p>A special mention goes to Ben Scholfield for giving the team some much needed pace on the wing and up front.</p>

<p>Next week’s fixture is against Llandudno away – I have a funny feeling that Manterfield will be unavailable!</p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>

<p> </p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
