<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Peter McNaught | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/peter-mcnaught/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-28T09:41:49+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Wilmslow]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-wilmslow/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-wilmslow</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1></h1>

<p>This weeks guest correspondent, Mr P McNaught.</p>

<p>The captain was obviously worried about whether the team would have difficulty finding the unusual venue of the Dev (the team being used to prime spot in the wet pitch) and so fixed a meet time of a full half hour before the match. He didn’t need to worry as the whole team arrived before any of the opposition! In fact the opposition struggled to find the way from the Club to the Dev. This meant that the trained athletes (eg the oldies – Gaune, West and McNaught) could show off their warm up routines.This was a weakened team as el capitain had been “mugged” at selection losing key players (Breton, Grant and Peacock) to the 5th team. However, we had 3 successive wins under our belt and confidence was high. The captain repeated his usual team talk “We can beat this lot”.</p>

<p>As the snow fell, the match began badly for Bowdon who were under pressure from the beginning with lots of poor passes and appearing to lack any sense urgency. However, the team started to put a few passes together and after a rare incursion into the “D” by McNaught were awarded a short corner. This was the first of a number of short corners which the team failed to convert – clearly something to be practised at the 6th team training on Monday.</p>

<p>However, the defence of West, Prosser, Fallon and Gaunce were steady throughout and Wilmslow hardly threatened the Bowdon goal. But the Bowdon attack could not convert. Manters was unusually off target and easy chances were missed. Jago and Brooks worked hard in midfield and Braithwaite played his usual pivotal <em>(pivotal – I like that!)</em> role in the middle. However, the goals did not come and the match ended a disappointing 0-0 draw.</p>

<p>Man of the Match was Fallon (Frank the Tank) for his steady defence and incisive attack.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
