<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Kyle Hatch | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/kyle-hatch/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-28T09:41:49+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon 5 v South Cheshire 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/09/21/bowdon5-v-south-cheshire-2/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-21T12:54:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/09/21/bowdon5-v-south-cheshire-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>First (long) match report of the season from our fearless leader. Never let it be said that he likes the sound of his own voice...</strong></p>

<p>A brand new season, a new division, new opposition and a new name. Bowdon 6 was now Bowdon 5, new and improved. After a successful season last year resulting in promotion. The goal this season is survival. Pre match it didn't start well. The lose of Goal Keeper Dave Jefferies and two of the solid back four in Peter McNaught and last season Man of the Season Chris Gawne certainly didn't help, we also lost last years quasi captain Frank Fallon, the team then lost actual captain Hatch to a stroke on Monday Night.</p>

<p>Their were positives. Some deadline day transfers were secured and two new members of the team made their league debuts. Will Corless and Ben Abbott came in to sure up the defence. Their was also a spot for the returning Ben Fallon, after a long injury. The goalkeeping crisis was solved by stealing a badger, James Mazarelo, affectionately known as Maza for typing purposes. After some interjection from Broken Captain Hatch, Acting captain Braithwaite re-jigged the line up to be:</p>

<pre><code>           Maza

Fallon, West, Abbott, Corless
         Braithwaite
      Bretton   Ankers
           Jago
   Manterfield Bailey

Subs: Prosser, Gadsby
</code></pre>

<p>New Manager Hatch took his spot on the sidelines, his personal Nurse accompanying him to make sure his blood pressure didn't rise too high.</p>

<p>Bowdon started out surprisingly fast. Showing previous unheralded pace and verve putting today's opposition on the back foot straight away. After being perennial slow starters last season it was a welcome surprise.</p>

<p>One other theme set early on was Cheshire understanding of how crap (slow) alty boys pitch really is. They hit everything, they might do this all the time, but today it worked wonders. Striking the ball cleanly, something Bowdon struggled with early on, a few mis-placed passes seeing the blood pressure rise.</p>

<p>Bowdon turned on the style soon, good movement down the left starting with Corless and Ankers allowed Jago to show off some skills before striking the ball inside the D, the umpire reliably informs me that the shot was going nowhere near the goal when it took a deflection off an opposition player and went in. The own goal rule now abolished any shot within the D counts if defected in, so this seasons first score was ...Dale Jago. Embarrassing to the 4 strikers in the team.</p>

<p>Cheshire soon reduced themselves to 10 men, one of their players landing hard and in his eyes dislocating his shoulder. The Qualified nurse on the touchline showed no compassion and neither did Bowdon, I did try to get him ice but no one form Alty boys was around. If only they'd bought subs.</p>

<p>Bowdon pushed on however and soon started getting short corners. Nick Manterfield marked his return to the team with a nice strike into the back of the net. Cheshire finally started to play some hockey at two down and Maza was introduced to Adult Hockey after wondering what all the fuss was about. The young lad making some fine saves at both his near and far posts.</p>

<p>Bowdon capitalised on the fine work at the back by continuing to push forward earning more short corners. I'm sure the third goal was scored here, but I can't remember who, West say, slotting home.</p>

<p>At this point Coach Brooks pointed out the good work that the team had done at training on Monday and how they were completely ignoring the tactics taught. Queue another short corner and a well worked slide ball left from Braithers, before Corless slammed home. A defender (actually) on the score sheet....</p>

<p>It should be noted that for large portions of the first half Nick Manterfield played left back....it was amazing to watch, not great for the blood pressure though.</p>

<p>Half Time: Bowdon 5's 4 – 0 West Cheshire 2's</p>

<p>After a rousing team talk and a slight tactical reshuffle. Bowdon went back out in search of more goals.</p>

<p>However it was West Cheshire who hit back first, some fine work moving the ball around the D forced a short corner from which they scored.</p>

<p>Bowdon re group quickly. Moving the ball well and with the theme of the second half being displayed regularly, both teams tiring long ball through the Swiss cheese middle creating a barrage of chances. Bowdon had to score and after a bit of a action in the middle involving Bailey, Manterfield and Prosser before Gadsby bundled home.</p>

<p>Cheshire tried to push back To stem the tide by they found keeper Maza in inspired form. Making a save with the kind of flexibility never seen before, at least not on the internet. He produced several more fantastic saves from short corners and pot shots.</p>

<p>Up next was contender for goal of the season. Another 3 on 2 break resulted in at least a short corner. From their the ball broke back to prosser at near top of the D. He lofted a slow looping ball back towards goal, the defender only needed to stand still for the ball to hit his stick but inexplicably took a Manterfield style swing and missed completely, the ball nesselled in the back of the net. Not since the opening day of last season had Bowdon scored more than 5 and they were out for blood.</p>

<p>But once again over eagerness to get the name of the score sheet cost Bowdon, far too high up the pitch a simple whack up field allowed South Cheshire to get their second of the game. Keeper Maza unfortunate to concede two.</p>

<p>Bowdon were not to be outdone and earned a questionable penalty flick. Good work from Nick Manterfield saw his burst into the D and attempt to get a shot away, an axe tackle from the wrong side should have been a short corner but referee Gareth was in a generous mode and gave a flick. Manters, checking for wind direction first, converted with ease.</p>

<p>With 15 to go, the shout went out to get more goals. Despite a number of 3 on 2 Bowdon failed to take their chance, making Manager Hatch very unhappy....blood pressure rose.</p>

<p>Manters did hit the back of the net again, but from just inside the Yellow football D and not the white Hockey D that he insists on telling everyone. I think it was just Hat-trick avoidance.</p>

<p>The only notable last action was for Neil Bretton to regale some wood chopping actions on an opposition player, earning him the first yellow card of the season. The final whistle went seconds later and Bowdon had their first victory.</p>

<p>Final Score: Bowdon 5's 7 – 2 South Cheshire 2's</p>

<h4>Man of the Match</h4>

<p>For some outstanding saves: James Mazarelo</p>

<h4>The Dale Jago Dick of the Day Award</h4>

<p>Neil Bretton, Yellow card no doubting. Although Hat trick avoidance from Nick Manterfield was a close second.</p>

<p>Brilliant performance from the boys today. But it should have been double the 7 we scored. Too many 3 on 2's. The strikers look like they never met each other. You don't need to score all the goals. Assists are fine.</p>

<p>Lesson To learn: Look up, not all the time, just some of the time, especially when your on the ball.</p>

<p>Special thank to Andy B, for taking over this week.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Wilmslow]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/12/01/bowdon-v-wilmslow/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-01T09:50:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2013/12/01/bowdon-v-wilmslow</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This week's match report is brought to you by the Scottish Captain.</p>

<p>The best men’s 6th team in Bowdon travelled the long difficult journey across the M56 to Wilmslow to play a 3rds team with very varied results. Bowdon knew going into the game that with a few ill timed trips on stag do's, exams and trips away, that the team would have a new look to it in places.</p>

<p>Thankfully three brave souls joined the current side to sure up the gaps and provide some valuable experience. With results going well for the team, hopes were high.</p>

<p>The team lined up with Jeffery in GK, Grant, West, Hawkins and McNaught across the back, Gawne on the right, Hatch left, Bray bottom and Braithwaite top of the diamond. Bailey and Gatsby were up top, leaving Prosser as super sub.</p>

<p>Bowdon started well, not put off by the slick passing of Wilmslow, putting pressure on them at 16's and side line balls. There were some early danger signs with quick breaks from Wilmslow but the defence held firm.</p>

<p>Bowdon were playing smart hockey, making the ball do the work. The ever energetic Gatsby winning (and taking) every free hit afforded him. From this good work a fine ball in from Braithwaite allowed, Hatch to ghost in. His effort just wide.</p>

<p>The first goal of the game came against the run of play. A long hopefully lifted ball seemed to be just stopping short of running long, Nick West smartly playing the ball into the players foot. Off that bounce the Wilmslow player put the ball in the goal. Players on both teams were astounded when the home umpire gave a goal.</p>

<p>Bowdon fought to come back from that injustice, but some sloppy finishing and variable ball speed passing saw chances come and go.</p>

<p>Wilmslow 1 – 0 Bowdon</p>

<p>A timely reminder from the captain, that for the last few weeks we'd gone in from behind and come back to win, along with some strong words of encouragement and reinforcement of team principles saw Bowdon come back out refreshed.</p>

<p>It was however Wilmslow that started much the better in the second half. The central midfielders starting to dictate play moving the ball across the park very well.</p>

<p>The midfield worked incredible hard to break down the Wilmslow play, frustrating them often. But when things are going against you, they go badly against you. An unlucky ricochet, saw the ball drop to a dangerous position and the forward slotted home.</p>

<p>Two minutes later it was three. Hoping to get back into the game Bowdon pushed forward and gaps appeared. An even foot race from halfway between their left back and Hatch, saw the Bowdon captain lose....badly. Out ran it left Grant out numbered at the back when a hit an hope ball crossed the D to be slotted home.</p>

<p>Trying to keep moral high Bowdon continued to push on. Karl Bailey was in fine form dribbling through some really poor tackles. Bowdon won a few short corners but were unable to find the goal, when on target found the Wilmslow keeper in fine form.</p>

<p>Some tired legs saw out the game, which ended in the first defeat for the mighty 6's.</p>

<p>Full Time: Wilmslow 3 – 0 Bowdon</p>

<p>Many thanks to all involved, you gave your all in difficult conditions. Special thanks to those who stepped up in our time of need. Their is a small bonus that Crewe also lost today. But it means Sale have closed the gap.</p>

<p>Man of the Match: Andrew Braithwaite – Excellent at the top of the diamond, fought back hard and won many tackles.
Dick of the Day: The only nom was for their umpire. Mainly for the most blatant foot of the season, not knowing which way to point when he gave a foul. Not knowing how far 5 meters was and not knowing what advantage is... apart from that he was OK.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Oxton]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-oxton/"/>
    <updated>2013-02-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-oxton</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1></h1>

<p>Mr Kyle Hatch presents Bowdon v Oxton…</p>

<p>Bowdon had won 2 in a row, could they make it 3. Things didn’t look good as there was no keeper on the team sheet, there was lots of talk of playing 11 outfield, with experimental 4-4-3 and 5-4-2. However upon arrival and the pre-match huddle, Braithers asked for a volunteer to wear the club kit, all eyes MAGICALLY turned to Hatch….wonder who gave them that idea….</p>

<p>Upon finally ‘volunteering’ he checked the club kit. Which leads to the amazing question of ‘how many 6 teamers does it take to remove shoulder pads from an idiots legs….’…at least 4. Finally after 5 minutes and some inpatient Oxton players the match began.</p>

<p>Bowdon started the match trying to restrict Oxton shots on goal. They did that by playing high tempo (for us) hockey that simple kept the ball away from the Oxton midfield. Too static throughout their 11, it wasn’t long until the scoring was opened. Some nice play saw Karl Bailey open his account for Bowdon from close range.</p>

<p>Having started the scoring Bowdon weren’t going to stop, it was non-stop pressure, with a high line defence keeping Oxton pushed back and soon it was two. Simon Brooks doing a lot of nonchalant dribbling all game decided it was time for his obligatory goal and hitting home. Twenty-ish minutes in, two nil and comfortable.</p>

<p>More pressure saw Bowdon earn a short corner which saw some imaginative play, the end result being Andy Braithwaite diverting the ball home with a great piece of skill/luck. (Delete depending on believability)</p>

<p>It took 30 minutes for Oxton to challenge the Bowdon keeper, a break from their right saw the winger run into the D with the ball. The Bowdon keeper charged out and deflected the ball wide, much to the amazement of the Bowdon team who’d never seen a keeper so mobile. There was talk after about a missed opportunity to ‘break the posh Scouser in half’.</p>

<p>The first real test of the first half for Bowdon came from a short corner, but Hatch easily kicked it away and the first half drew to an end.</p>

<p>Half Time: Oxton 6th 0 – 3 Bowdon 6th</p>

<p>At half time the captain once again congratulated the team on another great first half performance, but warned against last week’s complacency and gung-ho attitude from repeating. Queue a second half full of complacency and everyone trying to score…well almost everyone.</p>

<p>Oxton didn’t really try anything different than from the first half than give it to the kid with the headband who hit forward to strikers. Nick West and Simon Brooks contain any thought of a solid shot on goal for much of the second half. Bowdon did at least try to switch play from right to left and back again, but in between were bouts of irrational dribbling and weak passing.</p>

<p>Despite this Bowdon got a 4th. Brassington slotting home a smart shot after a decent save from the Oxton keeper. A 4th goal should of helped Bowdon push on after they showed what they could do, instead it was back to dribbling…and not always with the ball.</p>

<p>This lead to Oxton getting another short corner, the first a scuffed effort off a foot, the second a quickly taken affair which was deflected wide by the Bowdon keeper…a fine stop.</p>

<p>As the game toiled on the Bowdon defence seemed at ease, the back 4 of McNaught, West, Brooks and Prosser were quick to snuff out any real danger and this allowed the Bowdon midfield to release Bailey who knew the route to goal, knocking in Bowdon’s 5th.</p>

<p>A 6th soon followed, going down as another OG (second top scorer….sure with help he’ll over take Manterfield at the top). Dr Tom missed a great opportunity to get his name on the sheet, after beating the Oxton line and running into the D, decided to actually pass instead of shooting. Clearly missed the gung-ho memo.</p>

<p>The only sour note came from more sloppy play from the replacement Right back, Dale Jago. His mistake saw a 3 on 1 attack by Oxton. The players passed round the keeper before slotting home. 64 mins clean sheet….gits. Bowdon saw out the rest of the match with ease.</p>

<p>All in all another fine result by Bowdon 6th team.</p>

<p>Final Score: Oxton 6th 1 – 6 Bowdon 6th</p>

<p>Next week: Wilmslow 3rd’s HOME (SAT), Llandudno 2nd HOME (SUN)<br/>
Man Of The Match: ???</p>

<p>Well done guys, can we make sure that Dave is available every week please….if not, can we have a grown up’s kit if I have to play in goal again….</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Macclesfield 3 Match Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-macclesfield-3-match-report/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-14T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-v-macclesfield-3-match-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Written by Kyle Hatch.</p>

<p>Disclaimer; I still don’t know half the teams name, so much of this report will include clever writing to hide this fact…. or not</p>

<p>The game against Macclesfield III’s was meant with much anticipationafter last week’s heroics against Bangor University II’s. The pre-match traditional wait for Fallon got to ludicrous lengths as Frank hadn’t even made it to Bowdon by the time we left for the evening…a new record.</p>

<p>His mysterious disappearance from the starting list aside, Fallon was replaced in the starting eleven by Kyle “2.5 minutes” Hatch, who would endeavour to outlast his new nickname.</p>

<p>As has quickly become a season tradition, no warm was prepared and talks of ‘drills’ turn out to be nothing but crazy talk. Captain Braithwaite organised his troops and Bowdon prepared for battle.</p>

<p>A respectful minutes silence was adhered to in memory of a Macclesfield player who had passed away tragically at just 31….it is after all, only a game.</p>

<p>Bowdon started the brighter of the two teams, controlling possession through the middle and making good use of the right wing, Chen and Jago combining well….</p>

<p>Sustained pressure brought about some half chances but it took until 16 minutes for the first real chance and a goal. Again good work on the right and a lucky ricochet saw the ball break to Prosser (?) whose excellent dummy <em>(!?!)</em> left the goalkeeper flounding and a simple prod home saw Bowdon go one up.</p>

<p>Spurred on by their success and dominance Bowdon expanded their game to include the left side of the pitch, moving the ball around from wing to wing in an attempt to get more goals.</p>

<p>Bowdon’s offensive style almost cost them but great goalkeeping stop Macclesfield scoring on the break.</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper right'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/The-Wrong-Trousers-wallace-and-gromit-343158_500_375.jpg' width='200' height='200' alt='Kyle – perhaps these would help…' title='Kyle – perhaps these would help…'><span class='caption-text'>Kyle – perhaps these would help…</span></span></p>

<p>25th minute and the inevitable happened. Hatch’s legs gave up and he had to go off with cramp. Still a massive 10 fold improvement on the fortnight before.</p>

<p>The half time whistle came with more Bowdon pressure and despite winning at the interval, they felt disappointed not to be ahead by more. A sentiment echoed by the Captain, who’s comment of<br/>
disappointment about losing or evening drawing would come back to haunt.</p>

<p>Macclesfield came into the game with a 100% record and showed why second half, coming out a completely different team. Bowdon sat back and allowed them to attack. Despite some great defending the Bowdon goal was breached, an unlucky deflection sending the ball into the back of the net <em>(that may have been my knee…)</em>.</p>

<p>Bowdon strived to get back into the game and for the majority of the second half the game was even, both team’s looking for a winner.</p>

<p>With time running out Macclesfield looked the more likely, but superb defence including keeping out 3 penalty corners say the full time whistle go.</p>

<p>Final Score<br/>
Bowdon 6th 1 – 1 Macclesfield III</p>

<p>Man of the match went to Dave Peacock who’s calm under pressure in midfield help immeasurably. Honourable mention to Kieran Chen who’s driving runs from left back held relieve pressure and create chances.</p>

<p>Next week fixture: Northop Hall 3 (Away) <em>- Away game an no Manters!</em></p>

<hr/>


<h3>Note from the skipper</h3>

<p><img class="left" src="http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/premier-hockey-goals-22.jpg" width="200" height="200">
Just wanted to clarify – this is what a goal looks like. The ball is meant to go between the vertical posts and under the horizontal bar.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
