<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: James Tennant | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/james-tennant/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-26T21:15:06+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Crewe]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/01/05/bowdon-v-crewe/"/>
    <updated>2014-01-05T12:10:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/01/05/bowdon-v-crewe</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Match report courtesy of James Tennant...</p>

<p>This fine cloudy saturday afternoon at
south downs road, bowdon mens 6th team stepped onto the pitch. With a super early meet 40minutes before the game, a thorough team like warm up (minus mr 'under the thumb' dale) and a most inspirational talk from our esteemed captain, the first half was a bit of a disaster.....</p>

<p>One nill down at half time and play against us..oops. Without mentioning names it probably was dale's fault. 12.5 players isnt exactly idea for a top of the table clash..along with bobbly passes, standing off players in defence and an inability to transfer the ball to francis (cough JT cough).</p>

<p>After the first half 'warm up' and inspiration words from kyle, things picked up. Oh no wait...backtrack a bit. Nick, great pass to centre forward on top of the D. Good job he was scared shitless by the imposing figure of Dave in goal. Kyle - great control on the almost decapitating half volley. Dale - some fresh leg in the second half would have been good pal. Poor ben turned to 0.25 of a person.</p>

<p>Back on track...closer defending from peter helped limit the enemys attacking capability down their right side and some gutsy defending in the D limited scoring opportunities.</p>

<p>With a warmed up team, movement of the ball was much smoother peaking with some great attacking play from ben producing a 2v1 at th edge of their D. The ball reached dave brooks who slotted the ball into the bottom left of the goal. Ben, dave...jimmy would be proud.</p>

<p>A controversial goal proceeded this after some good attacking play down the right side led to a goal by andy...or was it andy? For sure, andy braithwaite takes credit with a good reverse stick chip, under pressure, over the keeper.</p>

<p>All in all a decent 2-2 result against top of the league...although another 5minutes and the enemy may have been defeated.</p>

<p>Bring on the rest of the season and good luck!! Shame dale will miss out such is life....</p>

<p>Congratulation kyle for being dick of the day.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
