<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: Frank Fallon | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/frank-fallon/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-28T09:41:49+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon 6 v Crewe Vagrants Match Report]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-6-v-crewe-vagrants-match-report/"/>
    <updated>2012-10-02T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/match-reports/bowdon-6-v-crewe-vagrants-match-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Courtesy of Frank Fallon…</p>

<p><span class='caption-wrapper left'><img class='caption' src='http://bowdon6.s.greenqloud.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/10/18163_longjohn.jpg' width='' height='' alt='Artist’s impression of Fallon’s injury' title='Artist’s impression of Fallon’s injury'><span class='caption-text'>Artist’s impression of Fallon’s injury</span></span></p>

<p>1st league game of the season and the Sixth team have had their first setback in their quest for mid-table mediocrity, losing 4-1 to the Crewe Vagrants.</p>

<p>The day started well for Bowdon as it wasn’t raining and the boys were eager to get going, some even turning up at the allotted meet time. However, shortly after pushback, things were already not going to plan with two players forced off with injury. Hatch took a nasty scuff to his nail varnish and was forced to leave the field indefinitely in search of an emergency manicure. Fallon, though, volunteered to carry on, despite being hit so hard with the ball that his Uncle John got a nose bleed.</p>

<p>Not long afterwards, Bowdon were behind, with Crew scoring against the run of play. The Sixes did go into the break, however, at 1-1 with Manterfield levelling with what is believed to be a first of many/only goal of the season.</p>

<p>After the break Bowdon pressed forward looking for a winner, and looked promising with Peacock pulling strings in midfield and Prosser strong at the back. It was not to be, however, as Crewe scored three more times to seal a close victory.</p>

<p>The Sixes will now have to look to next week and a trip to Wales, the British Middle Earth, to notch up their first victory of the season and the first under Braithwaite’s tenure as Captain.</p>

<p><em>Thanks Frank, an excellent Stalinesque rewriting of history. I think you’ve somewhat underplayed your part in Crewe’s second goal, but if you write the report you get to decide how the game is remembered…</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
