<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Tag: league | Bowdon Men's 5th Team]]></title>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/tags/league/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-10-21T11:27:42+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[The Captain]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Chester 4]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/15/bowdon-v-chester-4/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-15T08:54:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/15/bowdon-v-chester-4</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After the previous weeks heroics against the student horde of North Wales could the 5th XI continue their march up the table.</p>

<p>The drama started the day before with messages filtering through Facesplat that Carl ‘strongside’ Bailey had been locked out of his flat &amp; was in need of a home shirt.  Would he be able to aquire one &amp; get to the Grammar for the early meet-time?</p>

<p>Max remembered to bring his helmet &amp; to the shock of everyone Manters turned up for an away game, we suspect he misread the fixture a being a home game at the Grammar.  Having brushed off his protestations that Chester is not in his backyard we did point out that it wasn’t Wales &amp; a passport wouldn’t be needed.  The troops set off, whilst <del>Sergeant Wilson</del> Captain Ginger &amp; <del>Captain Mainwaring</del> Manager Kyle waited for Mr Bailey &amp; his missing shirt to arrive.</p>

<p>We arrived at Chester to be informed that Carl had still not found his shirt &amp; was still hunting for it all over South Manchester.  This forced the manager to put his kit on &amp; become part of the playing squad again, thus leaving us with 11 fit players &amp; 2 half crocked players on the bench (Ben F &amp; Kyle).</p>

<p>The game started with some good interplay by the 2 teams, noted by Jake &amp; Will linking up well.  During one of Chester’s early attacks Jiggles decided to turn his ankle leaving the 5th’s with only 11 fit players.  It was at this time that I’m reliably informed that Manters scored form ½ inch,  I think it was either Will C or it could have been from one of Jake’s jinking runs who slipped the ball past the onrushing keeper but I was distracted by Jiggles hobbling past.  During a couple of early attacks by Chester were thwarted by Max in goal &amp; the tough tackling from the defence.  Later in the first half Manters doubled his &amp; Bowdon’s goal tally this time from ¼ inch.</p>

<p>The second half started with Bowdon pushing forward &amp; Manters was surprised to receive the ball a foot out &amp; so subsequently missed out on getting his hat-trick.  Bowdon’s 3rd goal came from Ben F ghosting to the back post &amp; scoring from 2 inches out.  Late in the 2nd half Kyle decided that his presence was needed on the pitch, he muttered something about showing Manters how to score from the edge of the D.</p>

<p>Chester were thwarted at the other end by Max on multiple occasions but he was finally beaten by a well worked short corner.  Final score 3-1.</p>

<h4>Man of the match</h4>

<p>Max (another great performance from a young keeper)</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Bangor 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/08/bowdon-v-bangor-2/"/>
    <updated>2014-10-08T19:10:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/10/08/bowdon-v-bangor-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After last week's titanic struggle with Alderley Edge (match report Francis?),
the finest Men's 5th team in Bowdon needed to bounce back against Bangor Uni 2s
with a win to consolidate their league position.</p>

<p>The mighty 5s arrived early and talk quickly turned to which Bangor team would
turn up. Would it be the slightly drunk team beaten two seasons ago by the then
finest Men's 6th team in Bowdon; or would it be the team of highly trained
athletes that beat the afore mentioned 6s later in the season. Early indications
hinted that the students meant business...</p>

<p>The students started well with a solid 10 minutes of pressure, which left this
correspondant thinking it was going to be a long afternoon. This was before the
5s wunderkind James 'Mazza' Mazerello showed the students who was boss. His first
save was from point blank range, and the ball went to the student stiker's stick.
The second save was frankly amazing, and showed that there would be no easy goals
today. The student's heads noticably dropped and the super 5s got down to business.</p>

<p>The first goal was another well worked short corner routine (4th of the season).
The injection was wide, the pass to Bailey slow and the "cross" to Breton looping.
Breton took it in his stride and proved that he is deadly from six inches.</p>

<p>The second goal was a solo effort from new signing Jackson. He beat several students
and slotted home well, with Corless waiting for the pass that never came.</p>

<p>The third goal came from another short corner. Play Maker Braithwaite went route
one forcing the student keeper to play the ball onto his post man. Corless cooly
scored the resulting flick, giving the keeper no chance.</p>

<p>The student's got a couple, but we won't dwell on that...</p>

<h4>Man of the Match</h4>

<p>Mazza</p>

<h5>The Dale Jago Dick of the Day Award</h5>

<p>Frank, because Kyle decided.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon 5 v South Cheshire 2]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/09/21/bowdon5-v-south-cheshire-2/"/>
    <updated>2014-09-21T12:54:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/09/21/bowdon5-v-south-cheshire-2</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>First (long) match report of the season from our fearless leader. Never let it be said that he likes the sound of his own voice...</strong></p>

<p>A brand new season, a new division, new opposition and a new name. Bowdon 6 was now Bowdon 5, new and improved. After a successful season last year resulting in promotion. The goal this season is survival. Pre match it didn't start well. The lose of Goal Keeper Dave Jefferies and two of the solid back four in Peter McNaught and last season Man of the Season Chris Gawne certainly didn't help, we also lost last years quasi captain Frank Fallon, the team then lost actual captain Hatch to a stroke on Monday Night.</p>

<p>Their were positives. Some deadline day transfers were secured and two new members of the team made their league debuts. Will Corless and Ben Abbott came in to sure up the defence. Their was also a spot for the returning Ben Fallon, after a long injury. The goalkeeping crisis was solved by stealing a badger, James Mazarelo, affectionately known as Maza for typing purposes. After some interjection from Broken Captain Hatch, Acting captain Braithwaite re-jigged the line up to be:</p>

<pre><code>           Maza

Fallon, West, Abbott, Corless
         Braithwaite
      Bretton   Ankers
           Jago
   Manterfield Bailey

Subs: Prosser, Gadsby
</code></pre>

<p>New Manager Hatch took his spot on the sidelines, his personal Nurse accompanying him to make sure his blood pressure didn't rise too high.</p>

<p>Bowdon started out surprisingly fast. Showing previous unheralded pace and verve putting today's opposition on the back foot straight away. After being perennial slow starters last season it was a welcome surprise.</p>

<p>One other theme set early on was Cheshire understanding of how crap (slow) alty boys pitch really is. They hit everything, they might do this all the time, but today it worked wonders. Striking the ball cleanly, something Bowdon struggled with early on, a few mis-placed passes seeing the blood pressure rise.</p>

<p>Bowdon turned on the style soon, good movement down the left starting with Corless and Ankers allowed Jago to show off some skills before striking the ball inside the D, the umpire reliably informs me that the shot was going nowhere near the goal when it took a deflection off an opposition player and went in. The own goal rule now abolished any shot within the D counts if defected in, so this seasons first score was ...Dale Jago. Embarrassing to the 4 strikers in the team.</p>

<p>Cheshire soon reduced themselves to 10 men, one of their players landing hard and in his eyes dislocating his shoulder. The Qualified nurse on the touchline showed no compassion and neither did Bowdon, I did try to get him ice but no one form Alty boys was around. If only they'd bought subs.</p>

<p>Bowdon pushed on however and soon started getting short corners. Nick Manterfield marked his return to the team with a nice strike into the back of the net. Cheshire finally started to play some hockey at two down and Maza was introduced to Adult Hockey after wondering what all the fuss was about. The young lad making some fine saves at both his near and far posts.</p>

<p>Bowdon capitalised on the fine work at the back by continuing to push forward earning more short corners. I'm sure the third goal was scored here, but I can't remember who, West say, slotting home.</p>

<p>At this point Coach Brooks pointed out the good work that the team had done at training on Monday and how they were completely ignoring the tactics taught. Queue another short corner and a well worked slide ball left from Braithers, before Corless slammed home. A defender (actually) on the score sheet....</p>

<p>It should be noted that for large portions of the first half Nick Manterfield played left back....it was amazing to watch, not great for the blood pressure though.</p>

<p>Half Time: Bowdon 5's 4 – 0 West Cheshire 2's</p>

<p>After a rousing team talk and a slight tactical reshuffle. Bowdon went back out in search of more goals.</p>

<p>However it was West Cheshire who hit back first, some fine work moving the ball around the D forced a short corner from which they scored.</p>

<p>Bowdon re group quickly. Moving the ball well and with the theme of the second half being displayed regularly, both teams tiring long ball through the Swiss cheese middle creating a barrage of chances. Bowdon had to score and after a bit of a action in the middle involving Bailey, Manterfield and Prosser before Gadsby bundled home.</p>

<p>Cheshire tried to push back To stem the tide by they found keeper Maza in inspired form. Making a save with the kind of flexibility never seen before, at least not on the internet. He produced several more fantastic saves from short corners and pot shots.</p>

<p>Up next was contender for goal of the season. Another 3 on 2 break resulted in at least a short corner. From their the ball broke back to prosser at near top of the D. He lofted a slow looping ball back towards goal, the defender only needed to stand still for the ball to hit his stick but inexplicably took a Manterfield style swing and missed completely, the ball nesselled in the back of the net. Not since the opening day of last season had Bowdon scored more than 5 and they were out for blood.</p>

<p>But once again over eagerness to get the name of the score sheet cost Bowdon, far too high up the pitch a simple whack up field allowed South Cheshire to get their second of the game. Keeper Maza unfortunate to concede two.</p>

<p>Bowdon were not to be outdone and earned a questionable penalty flick. Good work from Nick Manterfield saw his burst into the D and attempt to get a shot away, an axe tackle from the wrong side should have been a short corner but referee Gareth was in a generous mode and gave a flick. Manters, checking for wind direction first, converted with ease.</p>

<p>With 15 to go, the shout went out to get more goals. Despite a number of 3 on 2 Bowdon failed to take their chance, making Manager Hatch very unhappy....blood pressure rose.</p>

<p>Manters did hit the back of the net again, but from just inside the Yellow football D and not the white Hockey D that he insists on telling everyone. I think it was just Hat-trick avoidance.</p>

<p>The only notable last action was for Neil Bretton to regale some wood chopping actions on an opposition player, earning him the first yellow card of the season. The final whistle went seconds later and Bowdon had their first victory.</p>

<p>Final Score: Bowdon 5's 7 – 2 South Cheshire 2's</p>

<h4>Man of the Match</h4>

<p>For some outstanding saves: James Mazarelo</p>

<h4>The Dale Jago Dick of the Day Award</h4>

<p>Neil Bretton, Yellow card no doubting. Although Hat trick avoidance from Nick Manterfield was a close second.</p>

<p>Brilliant performance from the boys today. But it should have been double the 7 we scored. Too many 3 on 2's. The strikers look like they never met each other. You don't need to score all the goals. Assists are fine.</p>

<p>Lesson To learn: Look up, not all the time, just some of the time, especially when your on the ball.</p>

<p>Special thank to Andy B, for taking over this week.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Brooklands]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/27/bowdon-v-brooklands/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-27T16:32:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/27/bowdon-v-brooklands</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On Saturday the best Men’s 6th team in Bowdon rallied for what we knew would be a tough game against a youthful Brooklands side.</p>

<p>After starting sloppy and inviting far too much pressure from the visitors, Bowdon found there rhythm and with a nice one-two down the right hand side of the pitch Breton finished off a training ground routine that would make Jimmy proud.</p>

<p>Brooklands levelled moments later though a well worked midfield effort and a lucky deflection. 1-1</p>

<p>Bowdon rallied and Prosser regained the lead for us after a powerful Braithwaite hit into the D which was neatly deflected by Brooks into the bath of Prosser at the far post for a tap in.</p>

<p>After “Words of Wisdom” from the captain (I think he had forgotten his book) we started the second half even worse than the first, inviting too much pressure and not giving the “fans” the free flowing exciting hockey they had become accustomed to this season. This resulted in us conceding another 2 goals without reply and trailing for the first time in the game.</p>

<p>Brooks then decided to have a go from the pushback, driving at the Brooklands goal beating several players (just) and checking back onto his strong side at the top of the D to get a shot away, which was deflected nicely into the well placed Gadsby to finish off and level the game up at 3-3.</p>

<p>A forgettable end to the game after that with neither side really pushing for that all important winner in fear of conceding at the other end. Game finished 3-3 which on the balance of play was probably a fair result with Brooklands dominating large amounts of the game with no final product and Bowdon showing moments of brilliance on the counter attack along with some resolute defending from the back four.</p>

<p>MOM – Brooks
DOD – I can’t remember but it’s usually Kyle!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bowdon v Sale]]></title>
    <link href="http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-sale/"/>
    <updated>2014-02-09T21:42:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://bowdon6.github.io/blog/2014/02/09/bowdon-v-sale</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Wind, rain and locked gates greeted the heroic Bowdon 6th team as they attempted to cement their top of the table position. Mindful of a tight game last time around the team buckled down quickly, moving the ball fluently and playing some liquid hockey of a standard usually only seen at international level.</p>

<p>Such was the level of concentration that your correspondent is not sure of the order of the goals scored or indeed the moves that led to them so apologies for any errors in the following.</p>

<p>Numerous chances were created and a lovely move down the right side produced the opener (I think) with the right back sliding a ball through to Breton who crossed incisively and manters got on the end of it.</p>

<p>Brooks then got the second following a scramble. That might underplay it and no doubt he will correct me if that's the case... It was a deserved goal to top off a strong performance.</p>

<p>During the first half there was a refreshing willingness from the home umpire to send off their players, although such was the professionalism of the keeper kicking the ball outside the D when Bailey was otherwise clean through that the yellow was the least that could be expected. Another yellow followed for the home team which may have been for deliberate feet, a warning that should perhaps have been taken on board by other players.</p>

<p>The high quality hockey continued and was rewarded by a third goal, this time from a short corner -a shot which may have been by Brooks being swept into the net by Braithwaite.</p>

<p>It was an excellent half of hockey against a strong team, with Grant and West contributing at the back with clearances round the post.</p>

<p>Hatch's team talk was admirably brief and included wise advice to avoid tempting the umpires to start sending our players off; advice that everyone heeded apart from the captain himself.</p>

<p>The second half proved a very different kettle of hockey sticks, with Bowdon starting slowly and allowing Sale to build some momentum. There followed a tough half with Bowdon working very hard and defending from front to back. Jeffrey was solid throughout making some good saves, but had no chance when Sale scored with around 20 minutes to go.</p>

<p>The pressure then got to Hatch who finished an energetic display 10 minutes early after cynically manoeuvring one of his enormous plates of meat to block the ball. (At least I only do it in training Kyle!) The captain was given a yellow and instantaneously awarded 'dick of the day'.</p>

<p>There was time for further clearances around and on to the post but  Bowdon held firm for the 3-1 victory.</p>

<p>All in all an excellent display with a combination of quality play and hard work throughout the team keeping Bowdon at the top of the league.</p>

<p>Joint MOM Brooks and Gawne</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
